選擇角色
捏人
太他媽棒了
你幹嘛把門關了  馬克西
爸爸  我六年級了
我有時候需要點  隱私
好吧  我要去機場了
兩天後回來
對你姐姐好一點
幫媽媽做點事
還有別碰無人機
我不碰  拜拜
我是認真的  那不是玩具
是我工作用的
知道了  一路順風  再見爸爸  愛你
謝了  來抱一下  小子
等你回來了我抱你兩下
我懂了
你笑什麼
你長大了
我很高興
不是  別笑了
我還記得從醫院把你抱回家的時候
就像是昨天
而現在你
已經開始手淫了
我沒  我不是
沒事啊  小傻瓜
就像你有了新玩具
世上最好的玩具
你只是想一直玩它
我只想讓你知道  我為你自豪
好了  做你的事吧  再見
愛你  兩天後見
艾米
你絕對不會相信
《好小子們》
兄弟們  知道嗎
我保姆告訴我
六年級所有人都打手槍
什麼是打手槍
就是姑娘給你擼到射
然後你要自己收拾乾淨
-我不覺得那叫"舍"
-沒錯的  "ㄕㄜ"  射
中學可比小學刺激的多
如果想平安渡過
我們必須團結一心
豆袋男孩一輩子
注意減速帶
你朋友是不是嫉妒你
在和大學男生談戀愛
-有些人嫉妒吧  -是嗎
你們在幹嘛
目不斜視  目不斜視
怪奇物語裡的小屁孩們  趕緊滾蛋
好吧  快走快走
你認識這些小屁孩嗎
暗殺神卡牌
沒有人能頂得住烏茲卡的屠爾贊
盧卡斯  別把它拿出來呀
兄弟  它值300美元
600了現在  我查過
600美元
-我們是百萬富翁了  -是啊
你們想不想
明天放學後去滑板場
我知道什麼是古柯鹼
安娜貝爾  出去
這裡僅限豆袋男孩
我聽說滑板場裡
那些大孩子會叫你吸毒
我們絕不吸毒
毒品毀了生命和社區
你沒有選擇
媽媽
安娜貝爾  別惹你哥哥了
走  上樓
快點
好了  豆袋男孩  收拾收拾吧
明天還要上學  8:30熄燈
什麼  你之前說是8:45
趕緊收拾吧
我不覺得我想去滑板場
我們現在六年級了
我們要開始做六年級該做的事了
你是不是想見布希麗
《Valentine》——YK Osiris
*你是否願意屬於我*
*是否想要我的心*
*女孩  成為我的情人*
我的天
媽
這公園真他媽的棒
你們快看  滑板車小分隊在呢
你們知道誰真的擅長嘲諷嗎
阿提卡斯·L  他很有趣
阿提卡斯·L
我和他對嘲的時候他屁話不敢說
對吧  馬克西
*但我需要你女孩  我得到了你*
*但你得到我了嗎*
*寶貝我在乎你*
所以呢
你要不要把你
為布希麗做的項鏈送給她
不要  閉嘴
我還沒有放進窯裡燒製呢
你總有藉口
索爾  你從來不和女生說話
女生會讓人分心
《搖滾時代》兩天後要試演了
*而我不想被束縛*
馬克西  過來
泰勒
大家都在說你在美術課上
給布希麗做了項鏈
得了吧  在我的美術作品完成之前
我不想討論
如果她對你有意思
你會承認你喜歡她嗎
她對我有意思嗎
不知道
我沒問過她
明天見
再見
該死
怎麼樣啊  戀愛中的男孩
她可能知道了項鏈的事
晚餐吃素菜千層麵
一切可真美好呢  盧卡斯
我們學校見
待會見
注意安全
滑板車男孩  滑板車男孩來了
酷一點
有事嗎  阿提卡斯
你們想看看很酷的東西嗎
當然
我們要幹什麼  要做什麼
我們要喝口啤的呀
怕了嗎
不怕
我喝過大概五千口啤酒了
窩囊廢  拜託
索仁是紀錄保持者
三口
三口嗎
有點上頭了
好喝
當心  很辣的
你到底喝不喝
我忘了  這週五我有音樂劇試演
他們要酒精測試的
索爾  就承認你害怕了吧  小屁孩
我才沒有
要不要我把啤酒
倒在奶嘴杯裡給你喝啊
奶嘴杯
不
好嘲諷  阿提卡斯
這不是好嘲諷
他爸爸被查到兩次酒駕
現在不得不坐火車上班
這才是好嘲諷
奶嘴寶貝  給我們唱首歌吧
不
不如
一閃一閃小窩囊
奶嘴寶貝
朋友們  他會喝的
他只是需要點時間考慮
奶嘴寶貝  奶嘴寶貝
再見
千層麵配汽水
別告訴我爸媽你們給我吃這些哦
這孩子可真搞笑
我們準備離婚了
什麼意思
別擔心  什麼都不會變的
我們保證
我們還會一起看
《我們這一天》嗎
當然  那是我們最喜歡的美劇
那是屬於我們家的美劇
除了一點
你會在兩個不同的電視上看
在兩個不同的屋子裡
所以你要每集看兩遍
那每週二的塔可呢
每週二的塔可還是依舊
事實上  你會有兩次每週二塔可  只是
有一個在週三
兩次快樂
雙倍快樂  雙倍塔可
所以  什麼都不會變的
我和你媽媽  我們還是朋友  對吧
我是說  作為家人一起吃塔可也很好
只是以後不得不換成週三了
*我漫步在陽光下*
《Walkin' on Sunshine》——Katrina
*陽光下*
*那感覺不是很好嗎*
*現在我每次走去信箱*
*我要盡力控制我自己*
*因為我等不及你寫信給我*
*你要來到我身邊*
索爾  優秀  天使的歌喉啊你
*我漫步在陽光下*
*漫步在陽光下*
我們在哪裡漫步
*漫步在*
*陽光下*
*那感覺不是很好嗎*
那感覺是很好  不是嘛
怎麼了
這歌我總是聽著傷心
別忘了
《搖滾時代》試演就在明天
這是我最喜歡的音樂劇
我做了一些大的調整
是根據我在怪萊塢的經驗
重金屬搖滾圈對好萊塢的戲稱
我想這會激勵
你們這些敢於夢想的人
太棒了
我看向她  但她在看其他方向
然後她看向了我
我又看其他方向
所以我想總有一天
我們會有眼神交流的
那很棒
這音樂劇會很讚
索仁  看啊
奶嘴寶貝在報名音樂劇
過分用力的人才會去唱歌
不是  是有人開玩笑報了我名字
我正準備劃掉的  看到沒
是啊  隨便了  窩囊廢
夠了
我們走
我還有地方要去呢
抱歉  索仁
別管阿提卡斯說什麼
他爸爸都不會報稅
這和阿提卡斯沒關係
從很小的時候
我一直想放棄唱歌
走了  我們要錯過魚排了
這是我見過最好的午餐
是啊  我爸媽現在變得超好  因為
因為
他們很好
他們很好  一切都好
那是新的耳釘嗎
是的  終於啊  感覺你的關注
你戴著很可愛
馬克西  我不喜歡可愛
我喜歡性感火辣
那是唯二我想要的
你喜歡嗎
你耳洞看起來感染了
在此排隊取餐
索仁太酷了
我聽說他痛打了德里克·巴哈曼
還讓他姐姐給他吹簫
他讓自己姐姐給他吹簫
不是  他讓德里克的姐姐給他吹簫
太他媽的傳奇了
我覺得索仁在叫我
有事
好
我聽說你喝啤酒很猛啊
我喝了挺大一口呢
不賴
明天晚上我要開個派對
這些傢伙們都會來
你來嗎
你應該來哦
相信我
好  我來
但是你懂的  我得先問我媽
補充一下  會是個熱吻派對哦
你法式深吻過女孩的  對吧
那當然了
親的哪
嘴唄
沒錯  老鐵
他不會就開始跟那些
受歡迎的小孩們一桌了吧
不會  我才是該去那桌的人
我們聽說大家叫你"奶嘴寶貝"
我們就是想讓你知道你可以
找學生反校園霸凌聯盟尋求保護
這個看著像奶瓶嗎
不啊
因為這他媽是盒果汁
因為我他媽不是小孩
太兇了吧
我能帶索爾和盧卡斯一起去嗎
他們也太遜了
不不  他們挺酷的
我是想保持男女人數平衡
懂我意思嗎  老鐵
明白  老鐵  但是
他們是我最好的朋友
我們幹什麼都一起的
我們是豆袋男孩
這名字還挺酷的
得了  帶他們來
我可以讓他們和我兄弟們一起玩
問好了你媽媽
記得告訴我一聲昂  老鐵
好的  待會見老鐵  拜老鐵們
怎麼樣
索仁請我們去參加他的派對
-索仁嗎  -對啊
他說了我的名字嗎
他說要請"索爾"
差不多吧
棒欸
對了  到時候會有女孩在哦
你明白什麼意思吧
狗血唄
接吻啊
所以
你們知道怎麼接吻嗎
-我沒經驗啊  -不知道
輸入"接吻"
不不  輸入"胸"
"乳腺癌研究"
"如何選對合適的內衣"
我有主意了
色情片
"你是否年滿18歲?"
我要點是
我們才沒滿18
這會成為我們的永久性記錄的
"我是你繼母
你不該看我洗澡的"
"別跟我爸說  他會叫我退出運動隊的"
"起來
起來"
他有麻煩了
"我要好好懲罰你
把短褲脫了"
有了繼母會發生這種事嗎
那不可能放得進去啊
快跑啊女孩
他手往哪放呢
我的老天爺啊
他們都沒接吻呢
是啊  反正嘴沒親
我爸媽有個練心肺復甦用的娃娃
我們可以用它練
來吧
這個心肺復甦娃娃長得好好看啊
那我先來囉
等一下
你在幹嘛
親她啊
沒經過本人允許不能隨便親別人
這可是開會說過的啊
假裝它是布希麗
紳士一點
好吧
布希麗  我能吻你嗎
為什麼呢
為什麼
對啊  你喜歡我哪一點
這個嘛
你很可愛
你聞起來香香的
你也很聰明
你總是推著亨利坐著輪椅散步
儘管他超刻薄的
當我以為自己已經
很瞭解你的時候
卻發現你還會玩滑板
我同意了
什麼感覺
黏黏的
她嘴裡為什麼有毛
知道嗎  這樣咱們學不到什麼東西
我們需要看真人怎麼接吻的
那是唯一能知道我們
親沒親對的辦法
我鄰居是個十足的色情狂
她總是換男朋友
她總放火嗎
不  你說的那是縱火狂
我說的是色情狂
無論哪裡都能做愛的人
真的嗎
我本來想明天再給你驚喜的
但我實在忍不到明天再說了
不用啊  又沒什麼事
不不  你一定想知道
我什麼都看不見啊
我知道自從我遇見本吉之後
咱們就沒怎麼在一起玩了
但是我想彌補你
所以明天  我要翹一天課
咱們開車到市區
去看肯德里克·拉馬爾的演唱會
沒開玩笑吧
我們還要吸茉莉[毒品]哦
你想的太周到了
那當然了  會很棒的
姑娘們
本吉幫我們搞到的茉莉
班傑明
謝啦
聽著
這不管用
興許我們應該去爬個樹
不行  他們會看見的
不是  我就是說
要不咱們爬個樹玩
哥們  等等
我有個辦法可以看到他們接吻
BD雷霆無人機
不行
它有攝影機
我們什麼都能看見
咱可以學技術啊
那是他爸爸工作用的
不是個玩具
當然是玩具
玩具店都有賣的
我叔叔在部隊裡飛無人機
現在他晚上睡覺
都會大吼大叫還總是狂拉肚子
他把這個留在家裡簡直是瘋了
你每天從它跟前過
-他在折磨你  -沒錯
就像你表姐
穿著比基尼走來走去還嘲笑你
如果他發現了  你會被關禁閉的
你就去不了索仁的派對了
更糟糕的是
你會失去你爸爸的信任
這也沒錯
她會愛上真實的你的
沒錯  但是吻功超爛
記得剛才的毛騙嗎
那個男的甚至都不會接吻
他只會舔那個女人的屁股
你想親別人的屁股嗎  馬克西
不想
馬克西  別聽他的
他只是因為沉迷於那些
受歡迎的小孩才想去的
馬克西  相信我
你不想還不會接吻
就去索仁的派對的
明天你們閨蜜時間結束之後
要不要來我這來點男人時光啊
我跟你說過了
這週末我要跟莉莉過
我知道  只是
見不到你我很難過的
因為你是我最好的朋友
但是莉莉是我最好的朋友
明白  完全瞭解
要不我跟我前女友瑪格麗特待會
你是想讓我嫉妒嗎
不是啊  你會嫉妒嗎
會的  這樣下去不行
我知道  你不夠辣
沒資格這麼作
所以下次你奇怪
好男人都去哪了的時候
記住這次
你讓一個好男人離開你了
你說什麼
我沒說話
我再也不想見到你了
你沒事吧
那男的去哪了
管他呢  兩個女孩擁抱呢
她們一定會接吻的
我們要不離近點
那是什麼
它在偷窺我們
-行了  輪到我了  -拿來
-她們發現你了  -不要
你會摔壞它的
你想要  好
接住了
不
該死
什麼鬼  索爾
咱倆都有錯
我爸會殺了我的  怎麼辦
我們就說有人入室搶劫
砸了家搶了無人機
那是我聽過最他媽蠢的注意了
夥伴們  夥伴們
我們只要說出真相就好了
上帝會站在我們這邊的
你們好丫  需要幫忙嗎
希望可以  女士
我們用無人機
跟著一家小烏龜來著
然後好像把無人機
掉在你家後院了
是呢  在我家  進來吧
你們喜歡小烏龜
-是啊  -那很好啊
別演了  賤人們
該死  是個圈套
你覺得我他媽在乎烏龜嗎
對不起
我們就是想學怎麼接吻
盧卡斯
那跟她們沒有關係
我們應該實話實說
我們要去一個熱吻派對
但是我們都不會接吻
我們可害怕了
老天爺啊  盧卡斯
我已經做過愛了
但是我沒親過女孩
就上網搜索"如何接吻"不行嗎
大家都這麼幹啊
簡單的很啊
求你們了
我們能把無人機拿回去嗎
那是BD雷霆無人機
是我爸爸的  他工作要用的
求你們還給我吧
我真的需要拿回去  求你們了
我覺得不行
你們要是不還我
我就告訴我爸你們偷走的
那我就告訴他你是個變態
我還要告訴全校的人
這是性騷擾
我會告訴所有人你有厭女症
我才沒給別人按摩[同音]過呢
這就是你不尊重女人的後果
我尊重女人啊
我媽媽是我最好的朋友
那我呢
我完蛋了
我爸會殺了我的
誰讓你非得偷窺她們
你個女權主義者
我不是女權主義者
我愛女人
我爸媽一定會給
你們的爸媽打電話的
我們都會被關禁閉的
更別想去索仁的派對了
我們完蛋了
你笑什麼  這明明就是你的錯
這是籌碼
沒錯
這是什麼
我也不知道
這是衛生棉條
幹嘛的
女生們害怕生出孩子
就拿來塞進屁眼裡
一個八年級的告訴我的
人類的身體構造真是個謎
兒童維他命咀嚼片
他們居然還在吃咀嚼片
軟糖好吃多了
我就喜歡吃咀嚼片
給我來一片
去他媽的防孩童瓶蓋
索爾  索爾
莉莉
那兩個女孩打來的
你好
你們偷了我的包
裡面有駕照  手機
馬上給老娘還回來
你他媽別吵
先把我的無人機還給我
讓我來  讓我來
你剛剛說什麼呢  小賤人
你要敢不聽話
我讓你吃不了兜著走
你為什麼這麼說話
漢娜  我可是有弟弟的人
這樣才嚇得住他們
你把我嚇個半死
聽著  我們只是想給你們個教訓
我保證會把無人機還你
不可能  她們還會騙我們的
或者直接制服我們
天啊  他們要是吃了茉莉怎麼辦
他們不可能打開的
他們還是小屁孩  吃了會死的
還是我  馬克西
你們到約翰·亞當斯雕像
對面的遊樂場來
明早7點40
拿上無人機
可別想糊弄我們豆袋男孩
很強硬
相當強硬
面對強硬的人就得更強硬
我們還沒掛斷呢
我靠
快掛斷
別再靠近了
為什麼
因為你們能制服住我們
把無人機放到滑梯上
然後把眼睛閉上  從100開始倒數
別想玩什麼小把戲
大伙都看著呢
臭小子  我們還要出遠門
趕緊把包還來  不然有你們好看
不要考驗我的耐心
威脅我們可對你沒好處  賤民
他媽的趕緊把茉莉還給我們
茉莉是誰  我們沒見過她
弟兄們  茉莉是春藥的名字
新聞頭條報導過
你們居然讓我們
把毒品帶到遊樂場來
這裡到處都是小孩
沒事  我知道該怎麼做
我們現在要進行公民逮捕
你們現在被逮捕了
-蹲下  -我的天啊
-把手舉起來  -不准動  舉起手來
-不准動  -舉起手來
快蹲下
蹲下
你剛剛是給你的假槍裝彈了嗎
你在嘲諷我嗎  你是在嘲諷我嗎
你現在說的每句話
都可能作為你的證詞
呈堂證供
你知道嗎
你們現在才是藏了藥的人
所以為什麼我
不對你們進行公民逮捕呢
靠
時間到了  癮君子
我的天啊
交易取消
我們不能再讓她們
拿著藥為非作歹
看看那些癮君子
她們的一生已經毀掉了啊
把藥給她們吧  然後拿回無人機
也許有個辦法可以保護社區
還能讓我們拿回無人機
先拖住她們
所以你們準備拿這藥幹嘛呢
吃啊
然後欲仙欲死
她們就是癮君子
沒錯
所以你們一輩子都在嗑藥嗎
每天如此
很好
你幹嘛呢
成功了
衝啊
我靠
算她們走運
我沒把她們打得屁滾尿流
天啊  她們找過來了
我靠
她們現在可是在學校裡呢
她們才不會管這麼多
她們磕嗨了
你們知道我們需要怎麼做嗎
別說出來  別說出來
學生反校園霸凌聯盟
-閉嘴  -反霸凌聯盟
-快閉嘴吧  -反霸凌聯盟
那是什麼
我們的生命受到了威脅
反霸凌聯盟  救命啊
-我們什麼也不怕  -我們沒事
快去上學吧  沒什麼好看的
這太瘋狂了
校園霸凌  惡中之惡
放下屠刀  回頭是岸
只要你傷害我們其中任何一員
你就是在傷害我們所有人
你的軟弱就是我們的力量之源
那幾個小屁孩偷了我的包
今天決不允許校園霸凌的發生
今天決不允許
-什麼鬼  -校園霸凌  惡中之惡
放下屠刀  回頭是岸
今天可真是我人生中
最有意思的一天
放下屠刀  回頭是岸
別擔心  之後再找他們算帳
反霸凌聯盟
剛剛在微博上圈了我們
先是被叫奶嘴寶貝
現在又搞這麼一齣
還有兩週我就六年級了
可現在社會人
所有人對我避之不及
弟兄們  我爸爸五點就回來了
如果我們不能在這之前
搞到一台新的無人機
我會被禁足的
也就是說我們都會被禁足
派對泡湯
也就親不到布希麗了
這輩子都被叫奶嘴寶貝
失去布希麗  失去朋友
失去希望  爸媽冷戰
被困在房間裡  孤獨終老
在週二吃兩份墨西哥捲餅
所以  馬克西
我們接下來怎麼做
我們要把課翹了
去搞一台新的無人機
別只會用你的大屌思考  馬克西
我們會被記過的  一輩子的汙點
馬克西的大屌
給我們指了一條明路
謝謝
如果其他人親了布希麗
我會死的
等等
我們應該這麼行動
我會拿瓶啤酒給索仁
然後我會喝一口
這樣所有人都知道
你是個酒鬼
那才棒呢
兄弟們  這附近唯一
賣那個無人機的地方
在北角免稅購物廣場
有6.4公里遠
6.4公里
我們他媽要怎麼過去
我們可以打滴滴
不行  這樣的話我媽媽會收到簡訊
她就會知道了
那我們騎自行車去
但是你哪來錢買一台新的
怎麼了
你懂的
我們那張烏茲卡屠爾贊的牌嗎
不可能
你說過是個人都想買我們的牌
那是我們的共同財產
作為朋友  那我們就一起賣出去
求你了  盧卡斯
豆袋男孩應該同舟共濟
好吧  你說的沒錯
-太好了
盧卡斯
-豆袋男孩要一輩子在一起
-對
我們真壞
我們真壞  我們真壞
我得把這藥扔了
你要幹嘛
把它扔了
我要把它扔進小溪裡
溪水會被汙染的
那我們就扔在森林裡
這可是春藥啊
如果一隻狐狸
吃了想操松鼠怎麼辦
它會死的
那我們要怎樣處理這些藥
就像我們怎麼處置嬰兒一樣
-打掉  -領養
不是
在我們去商場的路上
順便扔到消防隊門口
這主意不錯
有人要買我們的卡了
把我家地址給他們
我爸媽不在家
而且我家零食可好吃了
英雄之褲69
五分鐘之內就會到
我們準備一下
我在我爸媽衣櫃最深處
找到了所有這些武器
我還是搞不懂你為什麼需要武器
他可能是個戀童癖
他不可能對我們三個同時下手
他只用搞定一個
Anal beads  肛珠  成人性玩具
這是個什麼
快使用雙節棍  哼哼哈嘿
-真厲害
-這可不是玩具
打到了吧
怎麼聞著有股屎味
你好  我找盧卡斯
我就是
我叫克勞德
你好
我媽坐在那裡
那我們廢話少說
你是戀童癖嗎
什麼  當然不是
盧卡斯  如果你是個戀童癖
現在你面前只有三個小男孩
你會承認嗎
大概是不會的
那他為什麼會承認
你們真是夠了
我看起來像個戀童癖嗎
-是的  -非常像
這樣對我可不公平
你是我見過最像戀童癖的人了
聽著  我不是戀童癖
我是個好人
行吧
進來吧  先把鞋脫了
你帶著彩彈槍幹嘛
萬一有人對我們心生歹意
這卡片真精緻
你怎麼搞來的
今年夏天我搬到這裡來住
我  馬克西
索爾開始幫別人看狗
我們掙了八美元
我們拿這錢買了一個飛昇卡包
裡面就有這張卡
你們運氣真好
遇見馬克西和索爾
才是真正的運氣好
真不錯
我們給這個三人組
取了個名字  豆袋男孩
你知道為什麼嗎
因為你們有幾個豆袋沙發嗎
沒錯
我真是個天才
成交吧
來握個手
這樁生意就算成了
不行  我不賣了
什麼東西
-對不起  -盧卡斯
你給我滾過來
你們這些12歲的小屁孩
就是這樣做生意的嗎
你剛剛幹嘛呢
你不是同意了嗎
你說過只要一個人不同意
我們就不賣
我不同意
你為什麼這麼在意這張卡
那你為什麼不在意呢
這張卡片承載了我們很多回憶
你就打算這麼扔掉了
就因為你想親一個普通女孩嗎
太狂野了吧
布希麗不是普通的女孩
我們可能是要結婚的
結了婚反正到頭也是離婚
盧卡斯
我們二比一佔多數
盧卡斯  你現在正在氣頭上
布希麗可能就是我一生摯愛
打擾一下  夫人  能給我杯水嗎
夫人
呃你們幾個
關於她有什麼故事嗎
她是哪裡人啊
看起來很異國風情
給我聽好了
這筆交易我只說一次
400塊買她
不  我們要550
去你大爺的吧
那是我全部的零用錢
聽著  克勞德  咱們廢話少說
我媽是專門干生意的
我倆都心知肚明
如果你不想要這個娃娃
你早就已經走了
別把我們當小屁孩
我們知道怎麼搞買賣
你到底要不要
這個心肺復甦娃娃
一群傻子
我本來想出價一千的
只有我一個人覺得他
要草那個娃娃嗎
*我們房子裡有瓶子  車也叫好了*
*所以再給我倒杯香檳*
*戴著閃閃的金項鏈*
*數著籌碼  這局已經拿下*
*躁動的我  躁動的空氣*
*從沒想到金子會讓我這麼著迷*
*我們是賭徒  不磨嘴皮子功夫*
我們要補水
已經差不多騎了14分鐘了
我覺得這是我離家最遠的一次
我記得我在這附近
演過《貓》來著
你真的不打算唱歌了嗎
是啊  我從沒這麼開心過
乖乖把藥給我們
草  怎麼找到我們的
那部手機  他們裝了追蹤軟體
我們是不會給的
我們要交給消防員
你倆戒毒去
衝啊
我們開著車  蠢貨們
你們跑不過的
呵呵  我們這可是旋風單車
車進不來了吧  傻大姐
靠
*沒時間準備了*
*生活本就是一場噩夢*
你要去哪
*你躲得過初一躲不過十五*
你想藥想瘋了吧
把藥給她就行了
騎快點
我不會讓你毀了自己的生活
你沒事吧
你確定沒事嗎
發生什麼事了
我們的保姆在追我們
因為她想摸我們的雞雞
什麼  這才不是真的
-是真的  -不是
我沒有
-你就想摸  -我沒有
快走  走
-怎麼了  -走
走  走
盧卡斯  你沒事吧
我覺得我沒事吧
-你的手臂  -哇操
我叫急救來
不不  沒事的  這事他經歷多了
快來  我們得走了  得走了
得走了
單車我來搬
好了
我把手機扔草叢裡了
她們追蹤不到我們了
好痛啊
盧卡斯  你要小聲點
好  我們有冰塊嗎
沒有  我們他媽在一條巷子裡
止痛藥呢
我們可以讓他吃茉莉
不要
的確不行
不然他吃了會想著草我們
叫救護車來
任務終止
我們會被抓的
你有醫保嗎話說
我不知道  你有嗎
我不知道
我好像只有免賠額險
沒事的
這種事綜合格鬥選手經常碰到
我們只要把你的手臂
往牆上用力撞
把關節按回去
行吧  去他媽的  早死早超生
來吧  輕點
一  二  走
撞錯邊了
-找新網站  新網站  -好
好  躺下把手臂給我
來
好
上面說下一步會很疼
你應該找個東西咬住
我知道了
張嘴
好了
好  數三下
一  二  走
-泰勒簡訊你了  -她說什麼了
她想知道你為什麼不在學校
以及你今晚派對去不去
就說...
哦對不起正事
-我來幫下  -好
一  二  三
沒想到真成功了
你會沒事的  兄弟
不
我有事
我父母要離婚了
你幹什麼壞事了
-索爾  -怎麼了
對不起
我爸爸要搬出去了
不管你父母發生了什麼事
永遠有豆袋男孩給你撐腰
永遠不分開
豆袋男孩一輩子
保證
-保證  -保證
來吧  咱們去幫你買點兒童止痛藥
-需要幫忙嗎  小老弟
-不  我可以
行吧  幫幫我
嘿  邁爾斯
嘿  是準備上班還是剛下班
剛連值完三輪
我不在乎誰被搶劫了
我只是不想再去填那些表了
警察
我們身上有  得無  皮引
人家會拼音好嗎
正常點  假裝在聊天
-聊什麼  -正常點就行
你覺得政治怎麼樣
嗯這事挺複雜
那個警察好奇怪
他在視奸我們
正常點  倆超酷男孩在正常對話
我們翹課了
盧卡斯
我們有麻煩了嗎
本來我是要匯報上去的
但因為你們的誠實
這次就算了  好嗎
答應我別再犯了
保證  謝謝長官
好
真險
索爾呢
*我不是最強的  不是最混的*
*不是最硬的  也不是最高的*
*但我說的話都是真的*
*我走路都是最有型的*
*別惹我開口*
*沒人想惹麻煩*
*再這樣搞我*
*你怎麼樣都沒用*
站住
過來
你褲襠裡是什麼
我的雞雞
掏出來
我雞雞也很大的
放回去
老子今天心情好放你們一馬
我們還有毒品
他本來就盯上我們了
好吧  你們有什麼
一級管制類藥品
還潛在傳播的可能
大哥  這是維他命好嗎
還是兒童維他命
不  這是毒品
如果這是毒品  那這也是毒品
如果你不逮捕我們
我就要舉報你
-盧卡斯  -別他媽煩我了
我知道對小孩子說髒話不好
但是草他媽的
我逮捕你們也是因為
毀了我今天的好日子
好嗎  這給我
讓我回家吧
-他在叫後援  -我們怎麼辦
聽著
我決定了  我不想要孩子
怎麼了
那個警察盯上我們了
我們得殊死一逃了
我知道辦法了
不  這沒有商量餘地
你雖然是探長  官比我大
但婚姻關係裡  咱倆是平等的
那邊掛了  呵呵行八
免費  因為我是警察
*想像一下*
*我是一袋老二*
*送到你的嘴邊*
*我是變態*
*我能把熊寶寶打進屎裡去*
*嘴唇貼近我*
*我會讓你去院子裡拿棍子*
*捲一卷*
*我就是話題終結者*
你他媽怎麼回事  索爾
你根本不在意我的手臂
你只想著酒
我兩樣都在乎好嗎
是啊  在乎的是你和你的酒
現在我們成逃犯了
你吼我幹嘛
我現在還沒有祖傳單車了
週日騎車日全他媽毀了
你們看  看
商場
-耶  -太棒了
太棒了
來來
我日
我了個
去他大爺的
現在我們前有高速封路
後有警察圍堵
如果你不那麼腦殘的話
我們也不至於這樣
弟兄們  商場就在那
我們只需要橫跨高速
你看車都不怎麼動
考驗我們是五年級
還是六年級的時候到了
*沒人說話*
*沒人被嗆*
算了  我選擇撤退到林子裡去
大不了就喝雨水
吃松鼠過活  我不在乎
想都別想
天
這不就跟停車場一樣
等一下  你還偷了一瓶酒
你他媽怎麼回事  索爾
說得容易  反正又不是你倆
墓碑上還得刻上
奶嘴寶貝四個大字
好好說話  別亂噴唾沫行嗎
別上高速啊
小朋友經過
慢點  小朋友經過
你們在幹什麼啊
快回去
快快快
一群白癡
等一下  我收到簡訊了
是泰勒
她說馬庫斯會去派對
他超喜歡布希麗
她絕對會親他
他可是咱們年級的大暖男啊
等等  我才是咱們年級的大暖男
排名首先是我
馬庫斯  馬克西
然後才輪得到你
我可比馬克西暖多了
你才沒有
你去年把威洛比老師都弄哭了
不是我弄哭的
我只是拍了她哭的照片
大伙  大伙
瞧
媽呀
糟了
我操
咱們快回去
我們被困住了
我們要死了  要死了
我們不會的
只需要抓準時機  好嗎
只需要抓準時機
我們可以的
-加速  小瘋子  -天啊
我操  他成功了
我成功了
盧卡斯  現在看著我
我知道你很害怕
我不怕...一點都不怕
別說了  索爾
盧卡斯
別呀
我沒死
他過來了  哥們  快來
去你的
我也愛你
好了  快過來
我要媽媽
-加油  -加油
我沒事  我就住這裡算了
我很好
快來
你可以的
好吧
加油  索爾  你可不是奶嘴寶貝
你所向披靡
加油  索爾
我啤酒掉了
等一下
那是我爸的心肺復甦假人
我們沒殺人
我們安全了
沒有  耶
滴滴
勞駕
抱歉
讓一下  借過借過
我們之前打電話問過
BD雷霆無人機
真抱歉
賣掉了
哈哈  真好笑
不是  我真賣了
賣給了兩個姑娘
她們說認識你們
操你媽
我要殺了你全家
他糖是不是吃多了
我要把你全家變成殭屍
馬克西
我本來要解釋
結果被你打斷了
她們給你們留了個條
-他們為什麼要這麼走路
-不曉得
你們跟蹤我們
我把你們的包扔在樹叢裡了
傻了吧
你告訴過我們
如果你拿不到BD雷霆
你就完了
而且小孩子騎三輪腳踏車
只能到這裡
好了  毒品在這裡
把無人機給我
你他媽逗我
什麼鬼
這些全是維他命嚼片
我跟你說了她會檢查的
茉莉呢
去哪了
警察拿著呢
你把我們的毒品給了警察
等一下
我知道你們不瞭解我們
你覺得我們只是小屁孩
但聽著
你們無論遇到了什麼困難
毒品都不是解決辦法
毒品只能給你一種虛假的真實感
可能你覺得生活夠糟了
但你還有家人和朋友
愛你的人
你能不能閉嘴
我剛花了600塊
買了個白癡無人機
你毀了我的真情時刻
你說得很蠢
今天完蛋了
只有本吉有茉莉
他還不賣給我們
很抱歉  但我們完蛋了
我們可以買
可以給你們買毒品
我們才他媽不會
怎麼回事
你覺得他會給小孩賣嗎
我們不是小孩  是吞世代
（8歲至14歲的少年）
我們有什麼好失去的
成交嗎
馬克西  你瘋了
你應該就接受懲罰的
我和盧卡斯去派對好了
我們不會讓不懷好意的人
接近布希麗的
他們沒邀請你們
什麼
酷小孩們只邀請了我
你什麼意思
他們覺得你們有點...
平庸
但沒關係
只要他們瞭解你們了
他們就懂了
你們不平庸
你們很特別
我才不要買毒品
我也不要
你們不用去  我來說
你幫忙撐個場子就行
你是我們當中
唯一一個看上可能是大學生的
夥伴們
成交嗎
就為了一個接吻派對
你們做了這麼多
不  派對上還會有很多超酷的人
我還記著我第一次
參加接吻派對
那時是六年級暑假
在馬努什·佩特家
你親了誰
馬努什的妹妹
等一下  你沒在嗎
沒  那時我們還不認識
我們雖然是一個年級的
但是到八年級
我們才變成朋友的
我感覺你們肯定認識好久了
大家都知道
你在幼兒園會遇到死黨
對
那時你們交到了朋友是因為
你們住得近
還有你們父母是朋友
我們不是這樣的
我們是朋友是因為喜歡對方
還有我們住得近
還有我們爸媽是朋友
好了  過來
進去  買兩片藥
找本吉
別提到漢娜
誰是漢娜
我
我叫馬克西
我知道你叫什麼
就進去  買兩片藥
然後我把無人機給你們
如果出事了
直接開走
好
現在回頭還不遲
不行  我們得拿到毒品
這樣才能拿到無人機
才能去派對
有人嗎
我是你爹地
你是我的小嬰兒
沒錯  爹地
你要一直在這受罪
直到你學會當個男子漢
遵命  爹地
小嬰兒都穿什麼
紙尿褲
晚安
我們來找本吉
孬種  過來
好的  爹地
孬種
去叫本吉  有人找他
遵命  爹地
那是你兒子
你們幾個坐那去然後等一下
掉了要給我20塊  你這白癡
有事嗎
午安
我們想買兩片茉莉  麻煩了
是兄弟會的拉斐叫你們來的
就是他  那個白癡
你們只有七歲吧
除了你
我在經濟學課上見過你
好嗎  兄弟
說真的  我不給小孩賣毒品
我們不是小孩  是吞世代
誰讓你們來的
賣我們毒品  就跟你說
行
先坐著
你覺得要等多久
你讓我嗨了
告訴我誰讓你們來的
漢娜
怎麼了嘛  我嗨了
她原來覺得我是這種人
你們給漢娜說
如果她想要茉莉
就要給我口
你不能這麼跟女人說話
她只有同意了
才能給你口
你可以給我口
你也可以
那我呢  我就坐著嗎
我們可是豆袋男孩
什麼事都一起做
快滾  你們這群小屁孩
滾出去
大伙  等一下
我這邊有東西你可能會感興趣
有屁快放
白癡  現在誰是小屁孩了
-我操  -什麼鬼
不給我毒品  我就要被禁足了
我就永遠親不到布希麗了
馬克西
你他媽在幹什麼
你賣毒品
我們過來買
現在快賣給我們
別考驗我的耐心
行吧
你想要毒品  我又不是你爸媽  給
謝了
糟了
你他媽死定了
下面是怎麼了
她剛決定不起訴了
老天
我操
馬克西  小心
有我在  放心
索爾
老天  我剛殺了個人
盧卡斯  快拿毒品
我們沒有出現過
快開車
怎麼了
趕快走
什麼
開啊
快開
盧卡斯  毒品
不  不
讓我看看瓶子裡是什麼
說的對
趕緊給我吧
你們有點厲害啊
因為我們是豆袋男孩
那是什麼意思
我們有豆袋沙發
幹得不錯  小傢伙們
祝你們接吻派對愉快
謝謝
只有2.7公里遠
怎麼了
我們拿到無人機了
事情都解決了
馬克西
我帥臉被揍啦  行嗎
我們買毒品了
我們就不能直接回家嗎
朋友們  我爸電話
-爸爸  -小傢伙
飛機落早了
我十五分鐘後到家
現在的十五分鐘
還是再過會的十五分鐘
你這小傢伙真有意思
很快就見到你啦
我爸爸十五分鐘就到家
他可能根本注意不到
無人機沒了
他會的  他觀察力很強
所以我媽媽才愛上他
得在你爸爸到家之前
把無人機放回去
我知道
只有無人機
沒有你
好的
出發啦
我到了
-小心點  -我可以  我可以
隨風飛翔吧  馬克西
在前面這右轉
-我能看見你家
-就在那  那
窗戶關著
日  那怎麼辦
煙囪
這太窄了
你可以的
我看不見  看不見
鏡頭上全是菸灰
用原力
不  我可以的  我瞭解我家房子
我閉上眼都行
別弄壞什麼東西
相信我  我可以
你成功了
-我是有史以來最棒的駕駛員
-沒錯
-我們成功了  -太棒了
任務成功
爸爸
你安全到家了嗎
我真的不敢相信
我那麼信任你
我明確和你說了
不要碰無人機
我的上帝啊
我愛你
爸爸
爸爸  拜託
回我"我愛你"啊
我得聽你說
喂
我爸爸說我被禁足了
我再也沒有機會
親吻布希麗了
沒事的  馬克西
還會有別的派對的
盧卡斯  你沒有明白
他說的對   盧卡斯
這個派對會改變我們的人生
而你根本不在乎
這一點都不酷
好像你知道什麼酷一樣
你到底什麼意思
去嘬你的啤酒啊  奶嘴寶貝
我喜歡啤酒
我會去的
你可能覺得你可成熟了
可是事實是
你連陰毛都沒有
而我已經有六根了
你說你有陰毛
你還說你喝啤酒
而我知道你沒有
別吵了
承認吧  你翹掉音樂劇試演
因為你覺得那不酷
哪怕你擁有天賜的聲音
你總在誇大其詞
但從不能說到做到
就像在高速路上一樣
抱歉我不能穿過十二條車道
好讓你親吻什麼騷貨
日哦
她才不是騷貨
她是我一生摯愛
收回那句話
別上空手道啊
別打架
你絕不能用騷貨稱呼一個女人
你不能用任何東西稱呼一個女人
還有你
你讓我們逃學
帶著毒品到處跑
把一個警察用什麼東西
關在便利商店裡
我現在懷疑那是個假陽具
你他媽的看什麼呢  甘道夫
你們什麼都不懂
荷爾蒙在我身體裡亂竄
讓我做傻事
你們知道滿腦子
想著日樹是什麼感覺嗎
你覺得你比我們強
不是更強  是更成熟
我在追求戀情  把握當下
而你們還在玩著小孩把戲
我都不知道我們怎麼還是朋友
你喜歡的東西現在都取消了
生日派對取消
假期取消
夏天的活動都取消
凜冬將至
對不起  爸爸
不  你以後不准叫我爸爸
叫我安德魯  或者紐曼先生
或者典獄長
在你那副天使面孔下
隱藏著惡魔
我會永遠愛你
因為你是我的兒子
但我再也不會喜歡你了
索索
我剛跟馬克西的媽媽通了話
你知道他翹了課
還自己騎車去了商城嗎
-他那麼說的  -是啊
答應我絕不要做
那麼蠢的事
我答應你
然後我們穿過高速路
我的手臂脫臼了
一個女人模型從車裡飛出來
但我們還拿著毒品
然後我們用它換了無人機
然後馬克西開著那個
把家裡搞得一團糟
但那只是因為他想娶布希麗
但現在他不行了
因為他這輩子都要被禁足了
然後我們狠狠吵了一架
然後豆袋男孩解散了
然後  我有麻煩嗎
好吧  兒子  你看
我喜歡全是胡言亂語的故事
就跟別人一樣
我知道你正在經歷一段
充滿壓力的時期
但那不是你撒謊的原因
我沒有撒謊
我百分之百確定你在撒謊
我沒在撒謊
我想我知道發生了什麼事
你覺得你在失去我們
現在  你擔心
你還要失去你的朋友
看著我  我們會一直在這裡
別誤會我
我跟你媽媽都不是我們
初識的樣子了
得分開一段時間  但是沒事
你記著你的寄居蟹嗎
-赫爾曼  -對  赫爾曼
你記著他為什麼死了嗎
混蛋
你跟我說它跑了
也可以這麼說
它跑了  然後它死了
天啊  怎麼回事
赫爾曼死了
是因為寄居蟹蟹殼脫落之後
它們得在沙灘上找個新的
更大的貝殼來住
要不就會死  但我們不知道
所以赫爾曼是因為你們才死的
重點是
你和你的朋友在成長  在變化
你們都得去找更大的殼
這沒什麼不好的
好了  聽著  我們應該怪寵物商店
因為是他們沒有告訴我們
寄居蟹是這樣的
我是盧卡斯
你他媽的嚇死我了
我不想讓你父母看見我的臉
你在這幹什麼
我過去兩個小時成長了很多
我父母的離婚讓我改變很多
要是豆袋男孩不能一起長大
他們就會越來越分離
我不想那樣
我不想跟你們分開
那你就得去索仁的派對
你得溜出去
我不能  我被禁足了
而且布希麗的項鏈還在窯裡
我來操心那個項鏈
你父母能做什麼
翻倍禁足
布希麗是不是你永遠的愛
那你現在就跟我走
好吧  我跟你去
但我不要跟索爾道歉
他不來
挺好的
日他媽的小混球
我穿上外套
馬克西
怎麼
拿出點氣勢來
你說索爾不來的
他為什麼在這
父母算個什麼
我們現在要一起
搬進更大的寄居蟹殼了
我爸媽說的時候很有意義的
所以你一個人擔下了是吧
我想了想你會怎麼做
然後反著來
這場派對會是史詩級轉折
好吧  奶嘴寶貝
可別擋我路了  衛生棉
此品牌前半部分和max諧音
你們幾個小男孩真可愛
他們都在地下室
我都不想知道在底下幹嘛
快進來  小伙子們
你好
天啊  你來了
麥克西
我想讓你認識認識布希麗
你好  我是馬克西
你好
太好了  終於見到你了
你也是
外套挺酷
謝謝
我自己決定要這個的
當然我媽媽也在
我也跟我媽媽一起逛街
這一切進行的可真順利啊
你帶來項鏈了嗎
布希麗  這是給你的
謝謝
真好看
是月工的
真棒
我一會再戴這個
謝謝你  麥克西
你好嗎  奶嘴寶貝
不壞  也就是
跟一群男人打了場架
偷了瓶啤酒
奶嘴寶貝看起來可不像要喝它
我不止要喝它
我還要破紀錄
我要喝四口
不可能喝四口
索仁都不能喝四口
閉嘴
喝吧
這是一口
沒什麼了不起
這是兩口
行唄
第三口
簡直瘋了
他快要吐了
誰給他拿一個奶瓶啊
奶嘴寶貝  奶嘴寶貝
奶嘴寶貝
這是他媽第四口
我的天
索爾  索爾  索爾
我他媽是個酒鬼
四口  厲害
對索爾充滿了敬佩
眼睛看這裡
如果你不同意親嘴
那沒關係
你可以上樓去玩VR
但是如果你留在樓下
最好做好準備
因為我們要開始玩真的了
我們來轉瓶子吧
真好  我這裡正好有個瓶子
*還記得我們曾一起跳舞嗎*
*種種狀況和意外層出不窮*
*年輕時不懂因果總有聯繫*
*還一起高歌未唱完的曲子*
*那是激情的一刻*
我不玩了
你去哪裡
剛才那太噁心了
我要上樓去玩VR
如果你走了
你再也不能回來了
那可真是太慘了
布希麗
該你了
一定要是我  一定要是我
我的天  這大概是我見過
最狗血的一幕了
他不會親的
他會親的
我做不到
本性難移
他還是那個奶嘴寶貝
等等  是親嘴寶貝
親嘴寶貝
滾開  阿提卡斯
他的名字叫索爾
所有人都知道你媽媽
那本廚藝書是抄的
索爾  等一等
對不起我罵你用力過猛
不  你是對的
一直以來
我都努力成為別人
我帶了耳環
我喝了啤酒
我不唱歌了
想我今天也有點發瘋吧
我們離開這裡吧
不
你不想這麼做
你要留在這裡親布希麗
豆袋男孩所有事情都一起做
並不是所有事情
也不再是這樣了
也行這兩個大姐姐說得沒錯
也許我們走的路不同
也許吧
你準備怎麼做
我不知道
我只知道我們
不像他們說得那樣
絕不可能
這簡直瘋了
別管那瓶子怎麼指了
現在  走到那裡去
然後親你未來的老婆
再見
布希麗
我能親你嗎
可以
酷
我在哪裡
原來我在這裡
盧卡斯  我準備走了
你確定你不想試試這個嗎
不  我不用了
想去我的家裡玩
《暗殺神卡牌》嗎
我不想再玩《暗殺神卡牌》了
那我該和誰玩
你會找到人的
我的臉感覺好痛啊
不可能
我的天
這太棒了  真不敢相信你們...
在這裡
這真是太棒了
你們好
別  求你們了  別  別殺我們
發生了什麼事
你們怎麼認識索仁的
他是你的男朋友嗎
他是我弟弟
我愛死那個小混蛋了
你們  另外人呢
你們那個有悲傷眼睛的朋友呢
憂鬱男孩馬克西
在地下室裡親嘴呢
下面真是個亂交派對啊
你們倆對這個不感興趣嗎
好吧  沒關係  你們才6年級
你們總會想明白的
是的  你們有一生的時間
去做這件事
不急不急
你們喜歡什麼
《暗殺神卡牌》  規則
禁毒宣傳
烤乳酪
我現在也想要點烤乳酪
我可以去做烤乳酪
聽起來真棒
無袖男孩  你呢  你喜歡什麼
我喜歡唱歌
太好了
其實我今天還逃了試鏡
現在  我沒辦法參加了
不
什麼
你得說服他讓你參加試鏡
你必須  必須
為我們唱歌
不
我的天  為我們唱歌
為我們唱歌吧
所以  沒有烤乳酪嗎
獵酒者  為我們唱歌
*我得花一點時間*
*花一點時間好好想想*
*我最好仔細思索其中含義*
*以防我長大之後需要*
*現在我要爬過這座山*
*彷彿整個世界都壓在我肩上*
*穿過迷霧  看到愛的光芒*
*給這冰冷的人生帶來些許溫暖*
*我這一生*
*有心痛苦楚*
*我不知道*
*我能否再次面對*
*現在我不能停下*
*我已走得太遠*
*只為改變這寂寞人生*
*我想知道愛是什麼*
*我要你告訴我*
*我想感受愛*
*我知道你能給我*
*我要再花一點時間*
*花一些時間去審視自己*
*我已無處藏身*
*愛終於找到我*
*我的一生*
*充滿心酸痛苦*
*我不知道*
*能否再次面對*
*現在我不能停下*
*我已走得太遠*
*只為改變這寂寞人生*
*我想知道愛是什麼*
*我知道你能告訴我*
*我們談談愛吧*
*我想知道愛是什麼*
*心中感受到愛*
我的傑作
謝謝你  我是認真的
你好  馬克西
我馬上回來
你好  我沒想到你會來
你在搞笑嗎
你知道我從來
不錯過你的表演
你刺那個皮條客的時候
可真是太酷了
謝謝你
抱歉忘了  索爾  這是史考特
演得真棒
謝你  親愛的
我白天的時候更棒
我要去找凱西
我以為你還是被禁足呢
昨天就結束了
整整一個月
謝謝你為我背黑鍋
你也會為我做一樣的事情的
我的天
看看誰在這裡  我
-你好呀  -你好呀
趕緊我們已經幾週沒講話了
是啊
馬克西
我媽說如果你媽媽
來接我們的話
她會把我們放在冰霜凍優格
太好了  寶貝  我馬上過來
好的  寶貝
和史考特處得怎麼樣
挺好的
但也挺艱難
但是挺好的
處理好感情關係挺難的
但是別讓別人對你指手畫腳
嘿  盧卡斯
你仍然想等會和我們玩
《暗殺神卡牌》嗎
我馬上就到那裡
典型的盧卡斯
卡洛斯和那些反霸凌聯盟的人
看起來挺酷的
他們是很酷
但是他們不是豆袋男孩
馬克西
好吧
看來我得走了
嗯  好的  嗯
是的
我想你們了
我們做一個約定吧
即使我們不再一直一起玩耍
我們依然會在
重要的活動時候到場
豆袋男孩一輩子
等等
有樣東西我得給你們看
三分鐘之內
到我父母的房間裡來
朋友們  看這個
屋內鞦韆
你們會一直有最好的玩具
是的  關燈
怎麼樣夠酷嗎
你的父母真愛玩
他們用這個來幹嘛
他們在上面盪鞦韆
我們也可以上來嗎
當然可以
*我親愛的*
*親愛的  你怎麼愛我都不夠多*
*女孩  我不知道  不知道為何*
索爾
你在爸爸媽媽房間裡幹什麼
安娜貝爾  從這裡滾出去
那個鞦韆是用來做愛的
人們在那上面做愛
♪ Suave, no, no, no, sí ♪
Oh, fuck yeah.
Why's your door closed, Maxie?
Dad, I'm in sixth grade.
I need, uh, privacy sometimes.
Oh. Look, I'm heading
to the airport.
Be back in two days.
Please be nice to your sister,
help your mom,
and do not touch the drone.
- I won't. Bye.
- I-I'm serious, okay?
- It's not a toy. It's for my work.
- Yep.
Safe flight. Bye, Dad.
Love you.
Thank you. Hey.
Come give me a hug, bud.
I'll give you two hugs
when you get back.
I get it.
- Why are you smiling?
- Well, you're just growing up.
- It's exciting to me.
- It's not. Stop smiling.
I remember bringing you home
from the hospital
like it was yesterday.
Now here you are,
sexually masturbating yourself.
- No, I "F"-ing wasn't.
- Hey, it's cool, fool.
It's like you got a new toy...
the best toy in the world...
and you just want
to keep playing with it.
I don't know.
I just want you to know
I'm proud of you.
Okay, do your thing.
I'll see you later.
Love you.
See you in two days.
Amy, you are not gonna
believe this.
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Multimillionaire-aire,
multimillionaire, ooh ♪
♪ If you rich, put your
bust down in the air... ♪
Yo, guys, check this out.
My babysitter told me everyone
in sixth grade gets hand jobs.
What's a hand job?
It's when a girl jerks you off
until you "coom."
And then it's your job
to clean it up.
- I don't think it's "coom."
- Yeah.
C-U-M. "Coom."
Middle school's way more
intense than elementary.
If we're gonna get
through this,
- we need to stick together.
- Bean Bag Boys for life.
Speed bump.
♪ Multimillionaire, ooh. ♪
Are your friends jelly
you're dating a college guy?
Some of them, I think.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Wait, hey, c...
♪ Multimillionaire... ♪
- Can I help you?
- Retreat! Retreat!
Hey, Stranger Things,
go fuck yourself!
- Hurry!
- Go, go, go!
You know those fucking guys?
♪ Ooh. ♪
No one can stop
the Turzan of Uzkara.
Lucas, keep it in the case.
Dude, it's worth 300 bucks.
600 now. I checked.
- $600?!
- We're millionaires!
- Yeah.
- Do you guys want to
maybe go to the skate park
tomorrow after school?
I know what cocaine is.
Annabelle, get out of here.
Bean Bag Boys only.
I heard, at the skate park,
the older kids
will make you take drugs.
We'll never do drugs.
They destroy lives
and communities.
You have no choice.
Mom!
Annabelle,
don't antagonize your brother.
Come on, go upstairs.
Now... Hey.
All right, Bean Bag Boys,
finish up. It's a school night.
Lights out, 8:30.
What? You said 8:45.
Hey. Finish up.
I don't think I want to go
to the skate park.
We're in sixth grade now.
We need to start doing
sixth grade things.
Ooh, you want
to see Brixlee, don't you?
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ Do you want to be mine? ♪
♪ You know you on my mind ♪
- ♪ Be my Valentine ♪
- ♪ Can you be mine? ♪
♪ Valentine. ♪
- Hi.
- Oh, my God!
Mom!
♪ She gonna shake it, she gonna
shake it, she gonna drop that ♪
♪ We gonna keep on making
paper, we won't stop that ♪
♪ Hey, diamonds having
a conversation ♪
♪ Why don't you talk back... ♪
This park is fucking lit.
Yo, guys,
the Scooter Squad is here.
You know who's really good
at burns? Atticus L.
- He's so funny.
- Atticus L.?
I'd smoke him in a burn war.
Right, Max?
♪ You need me, but I need you,
girl, I got you ♪
♪ But do you got me? ♪
♪ Baby, I'd ride for you,
but would you ride for me... ♪
Ooh...
So, are you gonna give Brixlee
the necklace you made her?
No, shut up. It's-it's...
I haven't put it
in the kiln yet.
You always have an excuse.
Thor, you never talk to girls.
Girls are a distraction.
Rock of Ages auditions
are in two days.
♪ And I don't want
to be tied down. ♪
Max, come here.
Hey, Taylor.
People are saying
you made Brixlee
a necklace in art class.
Nice try, but I don't
talk about my art projects
before they're finished.
If she had a crush on you,
would you admit
you had a crush on her?
Does she have a crush on me?
I don't know.
I've never asked her.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
Fuck.
So, how'd it go, lover boy?
Uh, she might know about
the necklace.
Veggie lasagna for dinner?
Everything's coming up Lucas.
I'll see you guys at school.
Bye. Be safe.
Yo, Scooter Boys.
Scooter Boys. Act cool.
- Act... act cool.
- Okay, okay, okay.
What's up, Atticus?
You guys want to see
something cool?
Hell yeah.
What are we up to?
What are we doing?
We're gonna sip a beer.
- Scared?
- No.
I've had, like,
5,000 sips of beer.
Bitch, please.
Soren has the record.
Three sips.
- Three sips?
- Three sips.
Whoa.
I'm already feeling something.
Delicious.
Careful. It's hot.
Are you gonna drink it or not?
I forgot,
I have musical auditions
this Friday.
They drug-test for beer.
Thor, just admit you're
a scared little-wittle baby.
No, I'm not.
Want us to put the beer in
a sippy cup for you, Sippy Cup?
- No.
- Sippy Cup.
- Amazing burn, Atticus.
- It's not a good burn.
His dad has two DUIs and has
to take the train to work.
That's a good burn.
Sippy Cup, sing us a song.
No.
How about "Twinkle, Twinkle,
Little Bitch"?
Sippy Cup! Sippy Cup!
No, no, guys.
He'll do it, but he just
needs more time to think.
Sippy Cup! Sippy Cup!
Bye.
Lasagna and soda?
Don't tell
my parents you gave me this.
This kid is hilarious.
We're getting a divorce.
Wh-What do you mean?
Okay, okay, I'll tell you.
Everything gonna stay the same.
We promise.
Will we still watch
This Is Us together?
- Yes, of course.
- Yes.
That's our favorite show.
That's our family show.
Except now you're gonna see it
on two-two different TVs,
you know.
In two different houses.
So you're gonna have to watch
the episode twice.
What about Taco Tuesday?
Taco Tuesdays
are still going down.
Matter of fact, you're gonna
have two Taco Tuesdays,
just one on Wednesday now.
Twice the fun.
Twice the fun, twice the tacos.
It's... everything's
gonna stay the same, so...
Everything gonna be the same.
Me and your mom, you know,
we're still best friends,
right?
Mm-hmm.
I mean, it would've
been nice to have
tacos together as a family,
but how about this?
We could change it
to Wing Wednesday...
♪ I'm walking on sunshine ♪
- ♪ Walking on sunshine ♪
- ♪ Whoa ♪
♪ And don't it feel good ♪
♪ Hey! Na, na, na-na,
na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ Ooh... ♪
- ♪ Now every time I go for the mailbox ♪
♪ Gotta hold myself down ♪
♪ Hey! Na, na, na-na,
na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ Ooh... ♪
- ♪ 'Cause I just can't wait ♪
- ♪ Till you write me you're coming around ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
Thor, inspired,
voice of an angel, man.
♪ I'm walking on sunshine ♪
- ♪ Walking on sunshine ♪
- ♪ Whoa ♪
♪ I'm walking on sunshine ♪
- ♪ Walking on sunshine ♪
- ♪ Whoa ♪
- What are we walking on?
- ♪ I'm walking on sunshine ♪
- ♪ Walking on sunshine ♪
- ♪ Whoa ♪
♪ And don't it feel good. ♪
It does feel good, don't it?
What's wrong?
That song always makes me sad.
Don't forget, Rock of Ages
auditions are tomorrow.
It's my favorite musical.
I did make some
pretty big changes, though,
based on my time
in Holly-weird.
I think it'll really
inspire those of you
who dare to dream.
Sick.
So, I looked at her,
but she was looking
the other direction.
But then she looked at me,
and I was looking
the other direction.
So I think that someday
we're gonna make eye contact.
That's cool.
This musical is gonna be lit.
Hey, Soren.
Look at this.
Sippy Cup is signing up
for the musical.
Singing is for try-hards.
No, uh, someone signed me up
as a joke.
I was just crossing it off.
See?
Yeah, whatever, bitch tits.
Enough. Let's go.
- I have places to be.
- Sorry, Soren.
Don't listen to Atticus.
His dad doesn't even pay taxes.
Doesn't matter
what Atticus says.
I've been thinking about
quitting singing
ever since I was young.
Come on.
We're gonna miss fish sticks.
Whoa. That's the best lunch
I've ever seen.
Yeah, my parents are being
super nice because...
because...
they're great and...
they're great,
and ev-everything's good.
Ooh, wait.
Is that a new earring?
Yes, finally.
Thank you for noticing.
- It looks cute on you.
- Max, I'm not going for cute.
I'm going for sexy and hot.
Those are the only two things
I'm looking for.
You like it?
It looks infected.
Soren's so cool.
I heard he beat up
Derek Bachman
and blow-jobbed his sister.
He blow-jobbed his own sister?
No, he blow-jobbed
Derek's sister.
Fucking legend.
I think Soren's calling me.
♪ Uh, how we get down ♪
♪ Putting it down,
now you know ♪
♪ If you didn't know,
then I bet you know now, uh. ♪
- 'Sup?
I heard you sipped a beer
like a fucking champ.
Yeah, I took a pretty big sip,
actually.
Cool.
I'm having a party
tomorrow night.
All these fools are coming.
You in?
You should come.
Trust me.
Yeah, I'll come,
but, you know,
I'll have to ask my mom.
Also, gonna be a kissing party.
You've French-kissed
girls before, right?
Yeah.
Of course.
Where?
Their mouths?
Yeah, dawg.
He's not gonna start sitting
with the popular kids, is he?
No. If anyone should be
over there, it's me.
We heard kids were
calling you Sippy Cup,
and we just wanted to let you
know you can always call on
the Student Coalition Against
Bullying for protection.
Does this look like
a sippy cup?
No, it's a fucking juice box.
'Cause I'm not a fucking child.
That's so rude.
Wait. Can I bring
Thor and Lucas?
So random.
No, they're cool.
I'm trying to keep it
half girls, half guys.
You feel me, dawg?
I feel you, dawg, but...
they're my best friends.
We do everything together.
We're the Bean Bag Boys.
That's a dope-ass name.
Fuck it. Bring 'em.
I ride or die
for my squad, too.
Let me know
what your mom says, dawg.
Okay. Bye, dawg.
Bye, dawgs.
So?
Soren just invited us
to his party tomorrow.
- Soren?
- Yeah.
He said my name?
He said "Thor"?
- Pretty much, yeah.
- Sweet.
Oh, there's also
gonna be girls there.
You know what that means?
Drama.
Kissing.
So, do you guys know
how to kiss?
- I have no fucking clue.
- No.
No, not at all.
Type "kissing."
Ooh. No, no, no. "Boobs."
"Breast cancer research."
"How to find a bra that fits."
I have an idea.
"Are you 18 or older?"
I'm gonna click "yes."
We're not 18 or older.
This could go on
our permanent record.
I'm your stepmother.
You are not supposed to be
- looking at me in the shower.
- Don't tell my dad.
He'll make me quit
the sports team.
Get up. Get up.
He's in trouble.
You deserve a punishment.
Pull down your shorts.
Is that what happens
when you get a stepmom?
Ew.
No way that's gonna fit
in there.
Get out of there, girl!
Where did his hand go?
- Ew!
- Oh, my God!
Nobody even kissed.
Yeah, not on their mouths
at least.
My parents have a CPR doll.
We can go practice kissing
on that.
Come on.
This is
a really pretty CPR doll.
I guess I'll go first.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Kissing her.
You can't kiss someone
without their permission.
Remember from assembly?
Pretend it's Brixlee.
- Try to be a gentleman.
- Okay.
Brixlee, can I kiss you?
Why?
- Why?
- Yeah.
What do you like about me?
Well...
you're sweet.
You smell good.
You're smart, too.
You always push Henry
in his wheelchair
even though he's super mean.
And just when I think
I've got you figured out,
you go ahead
and start skateboarding.
I consent.
- How was it?
- Sticky.
Why does she have hair
in her mouth?
You know what? This isn't
teaching us anything.
We need to see
real people kissing.
That's the only way to know
if we're doing it right.
My neighbor is
a total nymphomaniac.
Her boyfriend's always over.
She starts fires?
No, that's a pyromaniac.
She's a nymphomaniac.
Someone who has sex
on land and sea.
Seriously?
Okay, I was gonna wait
till tomorrow to surprise you,
but can I just tell you?
- Nah, I'm good.
- No, you want to know.
Ugh. I can barely see anything.
I know we haven't been
hanging out much,
you know,
ever since I met Benji,
but I want to
make it up to you.
So, tomorrow,
I'm skipping school,
and we're driving to the city
to see Kendrick Lamar.
- Shut up!
- And we're gonna do Molly.
- You thought of everything.
- Of course I fucking have.
It's gonna be amazing.
Remix!
Well, Benji got us the Molly.
- Benjamin.
- Oh, thank you!
Look.
This isn't working.
Maybe we could go climb a tree.
No, they'd see us.
No, I just meant
let's go climb a tree.
Dude, wait.
I know a way
we can see them kiss.
I can't.
It has a camera.
We could see everything.
We can learn technique.
It's for his dad's work.
It's not a toy.
Of course it's a toy.
They sell it at toy stores.
My uncle flew a drone
for the Army,
and now he yells in his sleep
and has crazy diarrhea.
It's messed up that he even
keeps it in the house.
You have to walk by it
every day.
- He's torturing you.
- It's true.
It's like when your cousin
walks around in a bikini
and she taunts you.
If he finds out,
you'll be grounded.
You won't be able
to go to Soren's.
And even worse, you'll lose
your father's trust.
It's true, too.
She'll love you
for who you are.
Yeah, a shitty kisser.
Remember the porn from earlier?
That guy didn't even know
how to kiss.
He was just licking
that woman's asshole.
- You want to kiss an asshole, Max?
- No.
Max, don't listen to him.
He just wants to go
because he's obsessed
with popular boys.
Believe me, Max.
You don't want to go to Soren's
not knowing how to kiss.
So, tomorrow,
after you get some girl time,
why don't you come over
for some man time?
No, I told you I'm hanging out
with Lily this weekend.
Yeah, it's just...
you know, it's hard
for me not to see you,
'cause you're my best friend.
- But Lily's my best friend.
- Yeah, I get it.
Totally, totally get it.
Yeah.
I'll probably just hang out
with my ex, Margaret.
Are you trying
to make me jealous?
Uh, no.
Why? Are you jealous?
Yeah, this isn't working out.
I know. You're not hot enough
to be acting like this,
so the next time
that you're wondering
where all the nice guys went,
just remember
that you let one walk
right out the door.
What?
I didn't say anything.
I never want to see you again.
Are you okay?
Wait, where'd the guy go?
Who cares?
The girls just hugged.
They are definitely gonna kiss.
We might need to get closer.
Do you hear that?
What is that?
It's fucking spying on us.
- All right, it's my turn to fly.
- Give it!
- I just want to buzz 'em.
- No!
Hey, you're gonna break it.
You want it? Fine!
Shit!
Ha!
No!
- Shit! What the hell, Thor?
- That was both of our faults.
Well, Dad's gonna kill me.
What do I do now?
- Whoa!
- What the hell?!
- We say there was a break-in.
- What...?
They trashed the place
and took the drone.
That's the most stupid
fucking idea I've ever heard!
Guys, guys.
All we have to do
is just go over there
and tell the truth,
then God will be on our side.
Hey. Can I help you?
Uh, I hope so, madam.
We were using our drone
to follow a family of turtles,
and we thought it might have
crashed in your backyard.
Oh, yeah, yeah, it's here.
Come on in.
- So, you guys like turtles?
- Yeah.
- That's awesome.
- Time's up, motherfuckers.
Shit! It's a trap.
You think I give a fuck
about turtles?
We're sorry. We just wanted
to learn how to kiss.
Lucas, it's none
of their business.
We should have just
told the truth.
We're going to a kissing party,
and none of us have
ever kissed, and we're scared.
Goddamn it, Lucas.
I've had sex before,
but I've never kissed a girl.
Just go online and type in
"how to kiss."
That's what everyone does.
Oh.
It's very easy.
Look, can we please
have the drone back?
It's a BD Rolling Thunder.
It's my dad's.
He needs it for work.
Can I please have it back?
- I really need it. Please.
- I don't think so.
If you don't give it back,
I'll tell my dad you stole it.
And I'll tell him
that you're a pervert.
We'll tell the whole school.
This is sensual harassment.
We'll tell everyone
that you're a misogynist.
I never massaged anyone.
This is what happens
when you don't respect women.
I respect women.
My mom's my best friend.
What about me?
Oh, God, I'm so fucked.
My dad's gonna kill me.
You had to snoop on them.
You're such a feminist.
I'm-I'm not a feminist.
I love women.
And my parents are definitely
gonna call your guys' parents.
We're all gonna get grounded.
Forget Soren's party.
We're fucked.
Why are you smiling?
This is actually your fault.
This is leverage.
Oh.
Bingo.
- What is it?
- I have no idea.
That's a tampon.
- What's it for?
- Girls shove it
up their buttholes
to stop babies from coming out.
An eighth-grader told me that.
The human body
is truly a mystery.
Can't believe
they still eat chewables.
The gummies are so much better.
I like the chewables.
I want one.
Fucking childproof bullshit!
Thor! Thor!
Thor! Thor! Thor! Thor!
It's the girls.
Hello?
You took my bag.
It has my license, my phone.
Bring it back right now.
Fuck that noise.
I want my drone back.
I got this.
I got this, I got this.
What did you
just say, you little bitch?
I'll take a shit
down your throat.
Why are you talking like that?
Hannah, I have
a little brother.
- You're supposed to scare them.
- Well, you scared me.
Listen, we-we were just trying
to teach you a lesson.
I promise you we were gonna
give the drone back.
No way.
They could trick us again.
Or overpower us.
Oh, my God.
What if they take the Molly?
Then we wouldn't be able
to take it.
No, they're children.
They would die.
This is Max from earlier.
Meet us at the playground
across from John Adams
tomorrow at 7:40 a.m.
Bring the drone, and don't
fuck with the Bean Bag Boys.
- That was tough.
- Very tough.
I kind of got a boner
talking to those girls.
We're still on the phone.
- Shit! Fuck, fuck.
- What the shit?!
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
11, 12, 13, 14, 15...
Ow.
Don't come any closer.
- Why?
- 'Cause you could overpower us.
So, put the drone
on the slide, and count back
from a hundred,
and close your eyes.
And don't try anything funny.
There are witnesses.
Okay, we have a long drive
ahead of us,
so give us the bag
or I will hurt you.
Do not test me.
Threats will get you nowhere,
peasant.
Just give us the fucking Molly!
Okay. Who's Molly?
'Cause she's not with us.
Guys.
Molly is a sex drug.
Dateline did an exposé on it.
You had us bring drugs
to a fucking playground?!
There are children here!
- Shit.
- It's okay.
I know what to do.
We're making
a citizen's arrest!
You're both under arrest!
- Get on the ground!
- Sweet Jesus.
- Up, up, up!
- Stay still!
- Hands up! Hands up!
Get down now!
Did you just reload
your fake gun?
- Are you mocking me?
- Put your hands up!
Are you mocking me?!
Anything will be used
against you
- that you say.
- In court.
You know, you're the one
holding drugs,
so why don't I do
a citizen's arrest on you?
Fuck.
Time-out, crackheads.
Oh, my God.
Deal's off. We can't let them
put drugs back on the street.
Look at those dirty
fucking junkies.
Their lives are already ruined.
Let's just give them the drugs
and get the drone.
Maybe there's a way we can
protect our community
and get the drone back.
Stall them.
So, what do you plan to do
with those drugs, huh?
Take 'em and feel amazing.
They're addicts.
Yeah.
So, you been drugging
your whole life?
- Uh-huh.
- E'r'day.
Oh. Nice.
What's he doing? Hey.
- Yes! Yes!
- It's working!
- Yes!
Fly it to the school!
You're heading for the trees! Watch out!
We're gonna make it!
Fuck!
Those girls are lucky
I didn't kick their asses.
Oh, no! They found us!
- Oh, shit.
- They're on school property.
They don't care.
They're tweaking.
You know who we need?
- No, don't say it.
- We'll look like losers.
- Don't say it. Don't say it.
- SCAB!
- Shut up.
- Shut up. Zip it.
- Lucas, shut up.
- SCAB!
- What is that?
There's three boys in danger!
We're scared!
SCAB, help us!
We're okay.
- We're not scared. We're... we're fine.
- Lucas, shut up.
Just walking into school.
- Average day.
- Jesus Christ.
Bullying is wack.
Get on the right track.
When you attack one of us,
you attack all of us.
Your weakness
gives us strength.
- Well, those kids stole my bag.
- Not today, bully!
Not today.
- What the fuck?
- Bullying is wack.
Get on the right track.
This is the best day
of my life.
Get on the right track.
Don't worry,
we'll find them later.
SCAB just tagged us
on Instagram.
First Sippy Cup, and now this?
I'm two weeks into sixth grade,
I'm already a social piranha.
Guys, my dad gets back at 5:00.
If we don't get a new drone
by then, I'm grounded.
Which means we're all grounded,
which means no party,
which means no Brixlee.
- Sippy Cup for life.
- No Brixlee,
no friends, no hope,
parents fighting,
trapped in our rooms,
all alone, two Taco Tuesdays.
So, Max, what are we gonna do?
We're gonna ditch school
and get a new drone.
Stop thinking with
your big old dick, Max.
That could go on
our permanent record.
Max's big old dick is pointing
us in the right direction.
Thank you. If anyone else
kisses Brixlee, I'll die.
Wait, what?
Here's the plan.
I'm gonna bring a beer
to Soren's,
and I'm gonna sip that beer
so everyone will know...
That you're an alcoholic.
- That would be great.
- Guys.
The only place around here
that has one
is at North Point Galleria.
That's four miles away.
Four miles? How the fuck
are we getting four miles?
- You have Uber.
- No, it goes directly
to my mom's phone.
She'll know.
Then we bike.
Where are you even gonna get
the money for a new drone?
- What?
- You know.
Our Turzan of Uzkara card?
No way!
You said everyone wants
to buy it.
- We got it together.
- And we're gonna
sell it together, as friends.
Come on, Lucas.
Bean Bag Boys
do everything together.
Okay.
Guess that makes sense.
- Yes!
- Lucas! Bean Bag Boys for life.
- Yeah!
We're being so bad.
♪ We're bad, we're so bad ♪
♪ We're bad,
we're so bad ♪
♪ We're bad, we're so bad. ♪
I need to get rid
of these drugs.
- What are you doing?!
- Getting rid of the drugs!
I'm just gonna throw them
in the stream.
It can contaminate the water.
Well, then we can throw it
in the forest.
It's a sex drug.
What if a fox eats it
and tries to fuck a squirrel?
It'll kill him.
Well, then how do we
get rid of drugs?
The same way
we get rid of a baby.
- Abortion?
- Adoption?
No.
We drop it off at the firehouse
on our way up to the mall.
That's a really good idea.
Ah. I just got a bite
on our card.
Nice. Give 'em my address.
My parents aren't home,
and I have the best snacks.
PeterPan69 is gonna be here
in five minutes
to buy the card.
Well, let's get ready.
I found all of these weapons
in the back
of my parents' closet.
I still don't get
why we need weapons.
He could be a pedophile.
He can't molest
all three of us.
All he needs is one.
"An-al beads"?
Aka nunchucks, motherfucker.
Ooh.
- Yeah!
- It's not a toy.
Oh, shoot.
They smell like shit.
Hello.
Uh, I'm looking for Lucas.
- That's me.
- I'm Claude.
Hey.
That's my mom back there.
Hi-ya!
Let's cut the shit.
Are you a pedophile?
What? No.
Lucas, if you were a pedophile
standing in front
of three single boys,
- would you admit it?
- Probably not.
Then why would he?
Oh, come on.
Do I look like a pedophile?
- Sure do.
- Yes, absolutely. - 1,000%.
That's not fair.
You look more like a pedophile
than anyone I've ever seen.
Look, I'm not a pedophile.
I'm a cool guy.
Fine. You can come in,
but please take your shoes off.
You know, I've searched
the world for this.
Why are you bringing
the paintball gun?
In case anyone fucks with us.
This card is exquisite.
- How'd you get it?
- The summer I moved here,
me, Max and Thor started
a dog-washing business.
We earned eight bucks,
and we used the money
to buy an Ascension pack,
and this card was in it.
Well, you got very lucky.
The real luck
was meeting Max and Thor.
Fascinating.
We started calling ourself
the Bean Bag Boys.
- You know why?
- Because you had some beanbags?
- That's right.
- Yeah. Genius.
You got yourself a deal.
Let's go.
Let's make it happen.
No, I can't do this.
Sorry.
Lucas, get your butt
over here right now.
Excuse me, is this how all
12-year-olds conduct business?
What the hell just happened?
I thought you were cool
with this.
You said we wouldn't do this
if one of us wasn't on board.
- I'm not on board.
- Why do you care so much?
Why don't you care?
This card has
a lot of memories,
and you're just gonna
throw it all away
because you want to kiss
some basic girl?
Savage.
Brixlee isn't just some girl.
We're probably
gonna get married.
Every marriage ends in divorce.
Lucas, you're outvoted.
Listen, I can tell
you're lashing out with anger,
but Brixlee is probably
the love of my life.
Excuse me, ma'am. Can I get
a glass of water, please?
Hello?
Hey, guys?
Hmm.
Yeah.
What can you tell me
about her backstory?
Where is she supposed
to be from?
She seems quite exotic.
Okay, listen carefully,
'cause I'll make this offer
only once.
400 bucks to take her
off your hands.
No. We need 550, U.S.
Fuck off. What?
That's my entire allowance.
Listen, Claude,
let's just cut the bullshit.
I'm the son of a businesswoman,
and I think we both know,
if you didn't want
to buy the doll,
you would've left already.
Stop treating us like kids.
We know how things work.
So, do you want to buy
the CPR doll or not?
Fools.
I'd have paid a thousand.
Anyone else feel like
he's gonna fuck that doll?
♪ We got bottles in the house,
call it cabaret ♪
♪ So pour me up another glass of the champagne ♪
♪ I'm feeling right
with my ice and chains ♪
♪ Counting all these stacks
'cause we run this game ♪
♪ So hot that I can feel the fever ♪
♪ Never knew that money would make you a believer ♪
♪ Politickin', but we ain't
no politicians... ♪
Yee-haw!
♪ We got bottles
in the house... ♪
We should hydrate.
We've been biking for
almost 14 minutes straight.
I don't think I've ever been
this far from home.
I think I did a production
of Cats around here.
You're really not
gonna sing anymore?
Yeah.
I've never been happier.
- Just give us the drugs.
- Fuck.
- How'd you find us?
- Her phone.
They tracked us.
We're not giving you
these drugs.
We're giving them
to firefighters.
Get help.
- Go!
- We're in a car, dipshits.
You're not gonna outrun us.
Not on my fast bike, nerds.
♪ I don't live in my fears... ♪
Good luck getting your car
in here, losers!
Shit.
♪ I don't care if you care ♪
♪ I just know it ain't fair ♪
♪ Ain't no time to prepare ♪
♪ Life is just a nightmare,
Push ♪
Where are you going?
♪ You can run,
but you can't hide, Push ♪
♪ You can run, but
you can't hide, Push ♪
♪ You can run,
but you can't hide, Push ♪
♪ You can run, but
you can't hide ♪
Hey.
♪ Yellow motherfucking Claw ♪
♪ You can run,
but you can't hide... ♪
You're not getting
these drugs back!
Just give her the sex drugs!
Peel off!
I won't let you
destroy your li...
Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Lucas, are you okay?
- What the hell happened?
- We were running away
from our babysitter
'cause she was trying
- to touch our penises.
- What? That is not true.
- Yes, it is. - Yes, it is.
- I wasn't.
- Yeah, you were.
- I wasn't...
- Go, go, go, go, go! Go, go!
- What happened?
Go, go!
Lucas, are you okay?
I-I think I'm fine.
- - Your arm.
- Oh, hell no.
Yo, I'm-a call 911.
- Help! Help!
- No, no, no. It's okay.
This happens all the time.
Come on, we got to go.
We got to go. Go.
- Help! Ow!
- We got... Come on.
I'll get the bikes.
Okay. I threw their phone
in a prickle bush.
So they can't track us anymore.
Oh, the pain!
Lucas, you have to be quiet.
Okay, do we have any ice?
No, we're in a fucking alley.
What about pain medication?
- We have the Molly we can give him.
- No!
Yeah, he's probably just gonna
try and have sex with us.
Call an ambulance!
- Mission's over!
- We'll get busted.
- Plus, do you even have insurance?
- I don't know.
- Do you?
- I think I only have a deductible.
- It's all right.
This happens to MMA fighters
all the time.
We just got to ram your arm
into something very hard
so it pops back in place.
Fine! Fuck it!
Let's just get this over with.
Ow!
- Come on.
- Easy. All right.
One, two, three.
Wrong arm!
- Okay, new site, new site.
- Okay.
Okay, lie down on your back
and give me your arm.
Come on.
All right. It says
this next part's gonna hurt,
that you should bite down
on something hard.
I know.
Open. There you go.
Okay.
- On three.
- One,
two, three.
- Just got a text from Taylor.
- What'd she say?
She wants to know
why you aren't in school
and if you're coming
to the party tonight.
Just write...
Okay, sorry.
One, two, three!
Oh!
Let me help, let me help.
- Focus! On three.
- One!
Two! Three!
Hmm?
Wow. I didn't think that'd actually work.
You're gonna be good, man.
No.
I'm really not.
My parents are getting
a divorce.
What'd you do?
- Thor!
- What?
Sorry.
My dad's moving out.
Whatever happens
between your parents,
you always got
the Bean Bag Boys.
We'll never split up.
Bean Bag Boys for life.
You promise?
- Promise.
Come on.
Let's get you some
Children's Tylenol.
- Want some help, buddy?
- No, I got it.
Okay, just do it.
- Hey, Miles.
- Hey, man.
- Coming in or coming off?
- Just got off a triple.
Man, I don't care
if I get mugged.
I'm not typing up
any more paperwork today.
Cop.
Shit.
We have D-R-U-G-S on us.
He knows how to spell.
Just act normal.
- Pretend to talk.
- About what?
Just be normal.
What do you think
about politics?
It's a complicated issue.
This cop's acting weird.
He's eye-fucking us.
Just act normal.
Just laugh.
We're just
two cool guys laughing.
We skipped school.
Lucas!
Are we in trouble?
Yeah, well, usually,
I'd call this in,
but because you were
honest with me,
I'm gonna let you slide,
all right?
Just promise
not to do it again, okay?
We promise.
Thank you, sir.
All right.
That was a close one.
Wait, where's Thor?
♪ I'm not the madder,
the baddest ♪
♪ The hardest or the tallest ♪
♪ But I say what I mean
and I walk it like I talk it ♪
♪ Don't make me get started,
ain't nobody ballin', see ♪
♪ We keep getting up, it don't
matter that you're falling ♪
♪ No time for stalling... ♪
Hold it.
Come here.
What do you have in your pants?
My penis.
Pull it out.
I also have a big dick.
Put it back.
I'm being generous today.
- We also have drugs.
- Dude! -
- He was onto us.
- Okay, what do you have?
Schedule I
controlled substance,
with intent to distribute.
Brother,
these are vitamins, okay?
Children's vitamins, at that.
- No, those are drugs.
- No, look.
If that's drugs,
then this is drugs, too.
- If you don't arrest us, I'll report you.
- Lucas!
Just leave me the fuck alone!
I mean, sorry to fucking swear
at kids, but fuck.
You know, I'm gonna arrest you
for fucking ruining my day.
All right? I'll take them.
Let me go home!
- He's calling for backup.
- What do we do?
Hello. Listen.
I've decided I don't want kids.
- What's up?
- The cop's eye-fucking us.
We have to make a run for it.
I know what to do.
Well, no, it's not
up for discu...
Well, yeah, well, no, you may be detective,
but in the marriage
we're equal.
Wha...?
Just hang up.
Who cares?
This is free 'cause I'm a cop.
♪ Picture this,
I'm a bag of dicks ♪
♪ Put me to your lips,
I am sick ♪
♪ I will punch a baby bear
in his shit, give me lip ♪
♪ I'm-a send you to the yard,
get a stick, make a switch ♪
♪ I can end the conversation
real quick... ♪
What the fuck, Thor?
You didn't even care
about my shoulder.
- You just wanted a beer.
- I can care about two things.
Yeah, you and your stupid beer!
- Now we're fugitives!
- Why are you yelling at me?
I just ran off
without my family's bikes.
- Cycle Sundays are fucked!
- Guys, guys.
The mall!
- Yes! Yes! - Yes!
- We made it!
- Yes!
Come on, come on, come on.
- Oh, shit.
- Holy mother...
Goddamn it!
Great.
Now we're trapped between
a highway and the authorities.
Well, we wouldn't be
in this position right now
if you weren't such a narc.
Guys, the mall's right there.
All we have to do
is cross the highway,
and the cars
aren't even moving.
Now, are we fifth-graders,
or are we sixth-graders?
♪ Nobody speak,
nobody get choked, hey ♪
nobody get choked, hey. ♪
Well, I'm going back
into the woods.
I'll live off of rainwater
and squirrels.
I don't give a fuck.
Uh, no, you won't.
- Oh, my gosh!
- No, no.
It's-it's like
a parking lot, see?
Wait!
You stole another beer?
- What the fuck, Thor?
- Hey.
You guys aren't the ones
who's gonna have
"Sippy Cup"
on their goddamn tombstone!
God.
Say it, don't spray it.
Get off the freeway!
Children crossing.
- Please, children are crossing.
- Get off the road.
- What are you guys doing? Get back to the side.
- Go!
- Go, go, go, go. - Now.
- Fucking idiots!
Wait. I got a message.
Oh, it's from Taylor.
She said Marcus is
coming to the party.
He has a huge crush on Brixlee.
She's definitely
gonna kiss him.
- He's the nicest kid in our grade.
- Wait, wait.
I'm the nicest kid
in our grade.
It goes me, Marcus, Max, you.
- I'm way nicer than Max.
- No, you're not!
You made Ms. Willoughby cry
last year.
Hey, she was already crying.
I just took her picture.
Guys, guys! Look!
- It started.
- Oh, shit.
- Shit.
- Oh, fuck.
- Let's go back!
We're trapped.
Let us out!
I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die.
- No, we're not. We just need to time it, okay?
- Oh, fuck!
- We just need to time it right.
- Shit!
We can do this, guys.
We can do this!
N-No!
- Max, no!
- Are you batshit crazy?!
What the fuck are you doing?!
- Oh, shit. He made it.
- Oh!
I did it!
Lucas, Lucas,
look at me right now.
I know you're scared.
I'm not, at all...
Shut up, Thor!
- Lucas, fuck you! No!
- Shit! Shit!
Lucas!
No! Lucas!
I'm not dead!
- I'm not dead!
- All right.
- You got it, man. Come on.
- Yes! Yes!
- Fuck you!
- I love you, too.
Now, come over here.
I want my mom.
- Come on. Come on.
- Come on.
I'm fine.
I'll just live here.
- I-I'm good.
- Come on!
- You got this!
All right. Come on, Thor.
You are not Sippy Cup.
You're a badass.
Come on, come on!
Oh, shit! My beer!
Oh, shit!
- Oh!
- Oh, wait.
That's my dad's CPR doll.
- Oh.
- That's my dad's CPR doll!
- We're not murderers!
- Yes!
- We're saved!
- We're not fucking killers!
- We're not killers!
- Yes!
Beep, beep.
- Pardon me.
- Excuse me.
- Pardon me. Sorry.
- Hey!
Excuse me.
Got to get through.
Sorry.
Hey. We called about
the BD Rolling Thunder.
I'm so sorry, you guys.
Sold it.
Ha-ha. Nice joke.
So funny.
No, I did. I sold it.
Two girls, said they knew you.
Fuck you!
- Jesus.
- I'm gonna kill your family, and then they're
- gonna come alive...
- Ease off the sugar, huh?
- ...and turn your whole family into zombies!
- Max!
I was gonna say...
you didn't let me finish...
they left a note for you.
Why are they walking like that?
I don't know.
How'd you guys track us?
We threw your bag
in prickle bushes.
Dumbass, you told us
that your life would be over
if you didn't get
a BD Rolling Thunder,
and this is the only place
- a child could get to on a tricycle.
- Okay.
I have the drugs.
Now give me the drone.
Are you fucking kidding me?
What in the actual fuck?
These are just gummy vitamins.
- Shit.
- Told you she was gonna check.
- Fuck.
- Where is the Molly?
- Where is it?
- A cop has it.
You gave our drugs to a cop?
Wait. Look.
I know you don't know us
and you think
we're just stupid kids,
but just listen to me.
Whatever problems
you're having,
drugs are not the answer.
Drugs just give you
a false sense of reality.
You may think
your lives are bad,
but you have family
and friends who love you.
Can you shut the fuck up?
I just spent $600
on a fucking drone.
You ruined
my passionate moment.
- Well, it was stupid.
- This day is fucked.
Benji is the only one
who has Molly,
and he won't sell it to us.
Okay. Well, I'm sorry.
We're fucked.
We'll do it.
We'll get your drugs.
- The fuck we will.
- What the hell, dude?
Do you think
he would sell to kids?
We're not kids.
We're tweens.
What do we have to lose?
So, it's a deal?
Max, this is fucking insane.
Just take
your goddamn punishment.
Lucas and I
will go to the party.
We'll cock-block anyone
that gets near Brixlee.
They didn't invite you.
What?
The popular kids
only invited me.
What do you mean?
They think you're kind of...
random.
- Oh.
- But it's okay,
'cause once those guys
get to know you,
they'll see what I see,
that you're not random.
That you're specific.
I'm not buying drugs.
- Neither am I.
- You guys don't have to.
I'll do all the talking. I just
need your height in there.
You're the only one of us
that looks like
they could be in college.
Guys.
Are you in or out?
So, you guys did all of this
for a kissing party?
No. There's also gonna be
cool boys there.
I remember my first
kissing party.
It was the summer
after sixth grade
at Manush Patel's house.
Who'd you kiss?
Uh, Manush's sister.
Wait, you weren't there?
No, we didn't really
know each other then.
I mean, we were in
the same grade,
but we didn't really become
close until eighth grade.
Oh. I just figured you guys
- knew each other for longer.
- Yeah, everybody knows
you meet your best friends
in kindergarten.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, the only reason
you're friends with people
back then
is 'cause you live close
to each other.
Or, because, like,
your parents are friends.
No. That's not true for us.
We're friends
because we like each other.
- And we live close together.
- And our parents are friends.
Okay, come here.
Go in. Buy two pills.
Ask for Benji.
Do not mention Hannah.
- Who's Hannah?
- I am.
Oh. I'm Max.
Yeah, I know who you are.
Okay, just go in there,
buy the pills,
and then I'll trade you
for the drone.
Okay, if this goes bad,
drive off.
- Okay.
It's not too late to turn back.
No. We have to get the drugs
so we can get the drone,
so we can go to the party.
Hello?
I am your daddy!
You are my baby!
Listen, you will stay
down here and suffer
until you learn to be men!
Listen!
What you babies wearing?
- Diapers!
- That's right!
Good evening.
We're looking for Benji.
Hey, dickless. Come here.
- Yes, Daddy.
- All right, I need you to go find Benji.
Tell him he's got visitors.
Yes, Daddy.
I ask the fucking questions!
That's your son?
You guys can go sit your
asses down over there and wait.
Whatever happens to you is
your own fucking fault.
Drop and give me 20,
you fucking babies!
Listen!
Four! Get up!
Can I help you?
Good afternoon.
We would like to buy
two pieces of Molly, please.
Did Rafi from Sigma Nu
send you?
He did, that fucker.
You guys are, like, seven.
Oh, except for you.
I recognize you from econ.
What's up, man?
Seriously,
I'm not selling drugs to kids.
We're not kids.
We're tweens.
Who told you to come here?
Sell us the drugs,
and you'll find out.
All right.
Stay there.
Hey.
How long do you think
he's gonna be?
Oh, you made me high.
Ah.
Tell me who sent you.
Hannah.
What? I'm high as fuck.
So, this is what
she thinks of me, huh?
You can tell Hannah
that if she wants Molly,
she can suck my dick.
You shouldn't talk about
women like that.
The only time
she should suck your dick
is when she gives you consent.
You can suck my dick,
and you can suck
my dick, too.
What about me?
I'm just gonna sit here?
We're the Bean Bag Boys.
We do everything together.
Get the fuck out of here,
you little fucking babies.
Let's go.
Get out!
Hey, guys, wait.
I have something in here
that might change your mind.
Hurry up.
Pledges, listen!
Bitch! Now who's the baby?!
- Holy shit.
- What the fuck?
If I don't get those drugs,
I'm gonna be grounded,
and then I'll never
get to kiss Brixlee!
Max, what the fuck
are you doing?
You sell drugs.
We came here to buy them.
So now you're gonna
sell us the drugs.
Do not test me!
Okay.
You want the drugs?
I'm not your parent. Here.
Thanks.
Oh, shit.
Oh, you're fucking dead.
What the fuck's going on
down here?
Whoa!
She just dropped the charges.
Oh, God.
♪ You'd better run ♪
Holy shit.
♪ You'd better run
from the Devil's gun... ♪
Max, watch out!
I got your back.
Thor!
Your ass is mine!
Oh, my God,
I just killed a man!
Lucas, get the drugs!
♪ The Devil's fire ♪
♪ Just won't go out... ♪
We were never here!
Start the fucking car!
Max!
- What's happening?
- Fucking go!
- What?
- Shit, shit, shit!
Drive! Drive!
Lucas, drugs.
No, no, no, no, no.
Let me see
what's in the bottle.
Yeah. Of course.
Okay, just-just give it to me.
Wow, you guys are
little badasses.
'Cause we're the Bean Bag Boys.
I don't know what that means.
We have beanbags.
It's been real, guys.
Have fun at your kissing party.
Thank you.
Oh.
We're only 1.7 miles away.
What's wrong?
We got the drone.
Everything worked out.
Max.
I got punched
in the fucking face, okay?
We bought drugs.
Can we just go home now?
Guys, it's my dad.
Hey, Dad.
Hey, buddy.
I got on the early flight,
so I'll be home in 15 minutes.
15 minutes from now
or 15 minutes from later?
Ha-ha, funny guy.
I'll see you soon.
My dad will be home
in 15 minutes.
M-Maybe he won't notice
that the drone's gone.
He'll notice.
He's very observant.
That's why my mom
fell in love with him.
The drone has to be home
before your dad.
I know.
Just the drone. Not you.
Just the drone.
Okay.
Here we go.
- Yes!
- Careful.
- I got this, I got this. Oh!
Fly like the wind, Max.
Yeah, uh, take a right up here.
- I can see your house.
- There it is. There it is.
The windows are closed.
- Shit. What do I do?
- The chimney.
- It's very tight.
- You got this.
Shit! I can't see.
I can't see.
There's ash
all over the camera.
Use the Force.
- No, no, I can do this.
- Uh...
I know my house perfectly.
- I can do this with my eyes closed.
- Okay.
Don't break anything.
Trust me, I got this.
- Yeah!
- You did it! You got it!
- Yes!
- I'm the best pilot ever!
Yes!
- I think we did it.
- Yeah.
Mission accomplished.
Hey, Dad.
Did you get home safe?
Cannot believe I trusted you!
I explicitly told you,
- do not touch the drone!
- Uh-huh.
- Oh, my God.
- I love you.
Dad?
Dad, please...
say "I love you" back.
I need to hear it.
Hello?
My dad said that I'm grounded.
Now I'm never gonna be able
to kiss Brixlee.
It's okay, Max.
There'll be other parties.
- Lucas, you don't get it.
- He's right, Lucas.
This party could
change our lives,
and you don't even care.
It's not cool at all.
Yeah, you would know
what's not cool.
What the fuck does that mean?
Go sip a beer, Sippy Cup.
I love beer, so yes, I will.
And you may think you're
so mature, but the truth is
you don't have pubes,
and I have six.
You say you have pubes,
but you also say
you drink beer,
and I know you don't.
- Stop arguing!
- Just admit you skipped the audition
because you thought
it wasn't cool
even though your voice
is a fucking gift.
And you always talk a big game,
and you never back it up.
- Like on the freeway.
- Oh, sorry.
I didn't want to cross
12 lanes of traffic
so you can kiss some skank.
- Oh, shit.
- She's not a skank.
She's the love of my life.
You take that back!
Hey, no karate.
Stop fighting!
You should never
call a woman a skank.
You should never call
a woman anything.
And you...
You made us ditch school,
run around with drugs,
and lock a cop
in a convenience store
with what I now suspect
is a dildo!
What the fuck are you
looking at, Gandalf?!
You guys don't understand shit.
I have hormones
flowing through my body,
making me do crazy things.
Do you even know
what it feels like
to want to rub up
against a tree all the time?
You think
you're better than us.
Not better, just more mature.
I'm into romance
and grown-up shit,
and you guys are still
into little kid stuff.
I don't even know
why we're still friends.
Everything you like
is now canceled.
Birthdays are canceled.
Holidays are canceled.
Summers, canceled.
Winter is coming.
- I'm sorry, Daddy.
- No, no, no.
You are no longer allowed
to call me Daddy.
Call me Andrew
or Mr. Newman or Warden.
Underneath that cherubic face,
Devil lives inside you.
I will always love you
because you are my son,
but I no longer like you.
Thorny. I just got off
the phone with Max's mom.
Did you know he skipped school
and biked to the mall
by himself?
- He said that?
- He did.
Promise me
you'll never do something
as stupid as that, okay?
I-I promise.
And then
we ran across the highway,
my arm got ripped out,
and a fake woman
shot out of a car.
But we still got the drugs.
But then we traded
the drone for it,
and-and Max destroyed
his house with it.
But it was only because
he wanted to marry Brixlee,
and now he can't
because he's grounded for life.
And we got into a huge fight,
and the Bean Bag Boys
are broke up, and...
- Am I in trouble?
- Okay, son.
Now, look, I love a good story
with a bunch of gibberish
just as much as anybody, okay?
And I know you're going through
a stressful time.
But it doesn't give you
a reason to tell us fibs.
I'm not fibbing.
I'm 100% sure
you're fibbing to me.
- I'm not fibbing.
- Okay. I think I understand
what's happening here.
You think you're losing us,
and now you're worried you're
gonna lose your friends, too.
Look at me, man.
We'll always be there, right?
I mean, and look,
don't get me wrong.
You know,
me and your mom are not
the same people we were
when we first met.
Mm-hmm.
Tend to grow apart sometimes.
But-but it's okay.
You remember your hermit crab?
- Herman? Yeah.
- That's right. Herman.
- And you remember why he died?
- Oh, son of a...
You told me he ran away!
Technically, yes,
he ran away, but then he died.
Oh, my gosh. How?
Herman died
because hermit crabs
grow out of their shells,
and they need to find
new, bigger seashells
on the beach
to grow into, or they die,
and we didn't know that.
So, Herman died
because of you guys?
The point is...
you and your friends
are growing and changing,
and y'all need to find
bigger shells.
And there's nothing wrong
with that.
Okay, look, you need to blame
those pet store owners, okay,
because they did not give us
the information
about hermit crabs...
It's Lucas.
You scared the shit out of me.
I didn't want
your parents to see my face.
Why are you even here?
I've grown a lot
in the last two hours.
My parents' divorce
has really changed me.
If the Bean Bag Boys
don't grow together,
they'll grow apart.
I don't want that.
I don't want to get
a divorce from you.
Then you need to go
to Soren's party.
- You need to sneak out.
- I can't. I'm grounded.
Besides, Brixlee's necklace
is still in the kiln.
Let me worry about
the necklace.
And what are your parents
gonna do, double-ground you?
Is Brixlee your forever or not?
Then you need to come
with me now.
Fine, I'll go, but I'm not
apologizing to Thor.
- He's not coming.
- Good.
Fuck that bitch.
I'll go get my jacket.
- Hey, Max.
- Yeah?
Bring that dick.
You said Thor wasn't coming.
What the hell is he doing here?
I Parent-Trapped your asses.
See, now we're all in
a bigger hermit crab shell
together.
It made sense
when my parents said it.
So, you took the blame
for us, huh?
Yeah. I thought about
what you would do,
and did the opposite.
This party, it's gonna be
an epic rager.
Okay, Sippy Cup.
Just stay out of my way,
Maxi Pad.
Aw, don't you boys look cute.
Everybody's in the basement.
I don't even want to know
what's going on down there.
Come on in, fellas.
Hi.
Hi there. Oh.
♪ I never walk about
after dark ♪
♪ It's my point of view ♪
♪ 'Cause someone
could break your neck ♪
♪ Coming up behind you,
always coming ♪
♪ And you'd never have a clue ♪
♪ I never looked behind
all the time ♪
♪ I will wait forever... ♪
Oh, my God, you made it.
Max, I want you
to meet Brixlee.
Hi. I'm Max.
Hi.
It's nice to finally meet you.
You, too.
Cool jacket.
Thank you.
I got it all by myself,
with my mom.
I go shopping with my mom, too.
This is going so well.
Did you bring the necklace?
Brixlee, this is for you.
Oh, thanks. It's pretty.
They're an-al.
Ooh, fancy.
I'm gonna wear this later.
Thanks, Max.
What's up, Sippy Cup?
Not much.
Just, uh, got into a fight
with a bunch of men
and, uh, stole a beer.
There's no way Sippy Cup
is gonna drink it.
Not only am I gonna drink it,
I'm gonna break the record.
I'm gonna take four sips.
Four is impossible.
- Soren can't even do four.
- Shut up.
Drink.
That's one.
Big deal.
That's two.
Mm-kay.
That's three!
This is insane.
He's gonna barf.
Somebody get him a sippy cup.
Sippy Cup! Sippy Cup!
Sippy Cup!
Sippy Cup! Sippy...
That's fucking four!
Oh, fuck!
Thor! Thor! Thor! Thor!
Thor! Thor!
Thor! Thor! Thor!
I'm a fucking alcoholic!
No way!
Four sips. Badass.
Mad respect to Thor.
Eyes up here.
If you don't consent
to kissing, that's cool.
You can go play VR upstairs.
But if you're staying
down here,
you better strap in,
because shit's about
to get real.
- Hell yeah.
- Okay.
Let's spin a bottle.
Well, then it's a good thing
I got a bottle right here!
♪ Do you remember
when we used to dance ♪
♪ And incidents arose
from circumstance? ♪
♪ One thing led to another,
we were young ♪
♪ And we would scream together
songs unsung ♪
♪ It was the heat
of the moment... ♪
I'm out.
- Wait, where are you going?
- That was nasty.
I'm going upstairs to play VR.
If you leave,
you can never come back.
Oh, no.
Brixlee...
your turn.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Oh, my God. This is the most
dramatic thing I've ever seen.
He's not gonna do it.
He's gonna do it.
I can't do it.
People don't change.
He's still Sippy Cup.
Wait, wait.
Kissy Cup.
Kissy Cup!
Kissy Cup! Kissy Cup!
Kissy Cup! Kissy...
Fuck off, Atticus!
His name is Thor.
And everyone knows your mom
plagiarized her cookbook.
Thor, wait up.
I'm sorry I called you
a try-hard.
Nah, you were right.
This whole time,
I've been trying
to be someone who I wasn't.
I got an earring.
I drank a beer.
I quit singing.
Yeah.
I guess I went
a little crazy today, too.
Let's get out of here.
No.
You don't want to do that.
You're gonna stay down here
and kiss Brixlee.
The Bean Bag Boys
do everything together.
Not everything.
Not anymore.
Maybe those old girls
were right.
Maybe we're on
different paths.
Yeah.
Then what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
I just know it's not this.
No way.
This is insane.
Forget spin the bottle.
Now, go over there
and kiss your future wife.
Bye.
Brixlee, can I kiss you?
Okay.
Cool.
Where am I?
Oh, here I am.
Lucas, I'm leaving.
You sure you don't want
to try this?
Nah, I'm good.
Want to go to my house
and play Ascension?
I don't want to play
Ascension anymore.
Then who am I gonna play with?
You'll find someone.
My face feels so tingly.
No way.
Oh, my God.
This is amazing!
I can't believe
you guys are here.
Oh, this is so amazing.
- Hi. - Oh, hi.
- Sit down.
Please no, please no.
Don't kill us.
Look what happened.
How do you know Soren?
Is he your boyfriend?
He's my brother.
I love that piece of shit.
You guys,
where's everybody else?
Where's your friend
with the sad eyes?
- Sad boy Max.
- In the basement kissing.
It's an orgy down there.
And you guys aren't into that?
- Mm-mm.
- Aw, it's okay.
You're only in sixth grade.
You guys are gonna
figure it out.
- Yeah, you have your whole life for that. No rush.
- Yeah.
- No rush.
I mean, what do you love?
Ascension, rules,
antidrug campaigns...
grilled cheese.
- Mmm.
- Oh, I could fuck with a grilled cheese right now.
- Aw...
- Guys, I'm gonna make us grilled cheese.
- Oh, yeah. That sounds so good.
- Nice.
What about you, sleeveless?
What are you into?
I love to sing.
Yes.
I actually skipped
my audition today
for the musical.
- No.
- Now I can't be in it.
- What? You have to
convince them
to let you audition.
You must. You must.
- Audition.
- Shh. Sing for us.
- No.
- Oh, my God.
Sing for us.
You're a baby bird.
No, come on.
We missed our concert.
- Sing for us.
- So, no grilled cheese?
- Sing for us. Sing for us.
- No.
Be our concert.
♪ I-I gotta take
a little time ♪
♪ A little time
to think things over ♪
♪ I better read
between the lines ♪
♪ In case I need it
when I'm older ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Now this mountain
I must climb ♪
♪ Feels like the world
upon my shoulders ♪
♪ But through the clouds
I see love shine ♪
♪ It keeps me warm
as life grows colder ♪
♪ In my life ♪
♪ There's been
heartache and pain ♪
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ If I can face it again ♪
♪ I can't stop now ♪
♪ I've traveled so far ♪
♪ To change this lonely life ♪
♪ I want to know what love is ♪
♪ I want you to show me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I want to feel what love is ♪
♪ I know you can show me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I gotta take a little time ♪
♪ A little time
to look around me ♪
♪ And I got nowhere left
to hide ♪
♪ It looks like love has ♪
♪ Finally found me ♪
♪ In my life ♪
♪ There's been
heartache and pain ♪
♪ I don't know
if I can face it again ♪
♪ I can't stop now ♪
♪ I've traveled so far ♪
♪ To change this lonely life ♪
♪ I want to know what love is ♪
♪ I know you can show me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I want to know what love is ♪
♪ I know you can show me, oh ♪
♪ Let's talk about love ♪
♪ I want to know what love is ♪
♪ Love that you feel inside ♪
♪ I know you can show me ♪
♪ Whoa... ♪
♪ I want to know. ♪
My masterpiece.
Thank you.
I was really great.
What's up, Max?
♪ If I told you... ♪
I'll be right back.
- Hey. I didn't think you'd make it.
- Are you kidding?
You know I'd never miss
one of your shows.
It was so cool
when you stabbed that pimp.
Thank you.
Oh, sorry.
Thor, this is Scout.
- You were really good.
- Thanks, sweetie.
I was much better
in the matinee.
I'm gonna go find Cassidy.
I thought you were
still grounded.
It ended yesterday.
A month in the hole.
Thanks again
for taking the fall.
You would've done the same.
Well, well, well.
Look who's here. Me.
Hey!
Feels like we haven't
talked in weeks.
Yeah.
Max.
My mom said she'll drop us
at frozen yogurt
if your mom will pick us up.
Great.
Be there in a second, babe.
Okay, babe.
So, how's it going with Scout?
Good.
But hard. But good.
A relationship is
a lot of work.
Don't let anyone
tell you differently.
Hey.
Uh, Lucas, you still want
to play Ascension
with me and the guys later?
- I'll be there in a minute.
- Classic Lucas.
Carlos and those SCAB guys
seem cool.
They're cool.
But they're not
the Bean Bag Boys.
Max.
All right.
I guess, I guess I should go.
Yeah, all right.
Well...
Yeah.
I missed you guys.
Let's make a promise.
Even if we don't hang out
all the time,
we'll still always be there
for the big stuff.
Bean Bag Boys for life.
Bean Bag Boys
for life.
Wait.
There's something
I have to show you.
Come up to my parents' bedroom
in three minutes.
Yo, guys, check this out.
An indoor swing?
You always have the best toys.
Yeah!
Flip that switch.
How cool is it?
Your parents love to play.
- What do they do with it?
- They swing on it.
- Can we go on it?
- Fuck yeah.
♪ My darling, I ♪
♪ Can't get enough
of your love, babe ♪
♪ Girl, I don't know ♪
♪ I don't know why ♪
♪ I can't get enough
of your love, babe ♪
Thor?
What are you doing
in Mom and Dad's room?
Get the hell out of here,
Annabelle!
That swing is for sexing.
People do sex on it.
Oh...
♪ If you're down, boy,
really down ♪
♪ Baby, let me watch you
go to town ♪
♪ It's your one chance, baby ♪
♪ Never or now, yeah ♪
♪ Let me see you
go to town, baby ♪
♪ Go to town, yeah ♪
♪ Baby, let me watch you
go to town ♪
♪ It's your one chance,
baby, never or now ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Go down, go down, go down,
yeah ♪
♪ Let me see you
go to town, yeah ♪
♪ Go down, go down, go down,
yeah ♪
♪ Let me see you go to town ♪
♪ Go down, go down, go down,
yeah ♪
♪ Let me see you
go to town, yeah ♪
- ♪ Go down, go down, go down ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Go to town with it,
and she shave it all off ♪
♪ Charlie Brown with it ♪
♪ Lookin' all around ♪
♪ All the other girls
sound fishy ♪
♪ He ain't ever caught a whiff,
that's why he down with it ♪
♪ Yeah, bitch,
I'm telling you ♪
- ♪ What? Oh ♪
- ♪ This incredible ♪
- ♪ This shit edible ♪
- ♪ Okay ♪
♪ It's like caramel,
kiss my genital ♪
- ♪ Mine taste medical ♪
- ♪ Mayday ♪
- ♪ Hers like chemicals ♪
- ♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ If he gay, though, when he
taste that shit, turn hetero ♪
♪ Oh, my God ♪
♪ Can you see that
she need kneepads? ♪
♪ I'm a bad bitch,
fuck a pee-pad ♪
♪ Full of shit, if he don't
eat it, he a D-bag ♪
♪ He could use a submarine,
I'll call him seaman ♪
♪ Yeah, if you're down, boy,
really down ♪
♪ Baby, let me watch you
go to town ♪
♪ It's your one chance, baby ♪
♪ Never or now, yeah ♪
♪ Let me see you
go to town, baby ♪
♪ Go to town, yeah ♪
♪ Baby, let me watch you
go to town ♪
♪ It's your one chance,
baby, never or now ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah. ♪
♪ What? ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
- ♪ What? ♪
- ♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
- ♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
- ♪ What? ♪
- ♪ Hey. ♪